¶ MY FIRST ¶
¶ MY LAST ¶
¶ MY EVERYTHING ¶
¶ AND THE ANSWER TO ¶
¶ ALL MY DREAMS ¶
¶ YOU'RE MY SUN ¶
¶ MY MOON ¶
¶ MOON ¶
¶ MY GUIDING STAR ¶
WHOO, SING!
¶ MY KIND OF WONDERFUL ¶
¶ THAT'S WHAT YOU ARE ¶
¶ I KNOW ¶
¶ THERE'S ONLY ¶
¶ THERE'S ONLY
ONE LIKE YOU ¶
¶ ONLY ONE LIKE YOU ¶
¶ THERE'S NO WAY ¶
¶ THEY COULD HAVE
MADE 2 ¶
¶ THEY COULDN'T HAVE
¶ YOU THE ONLY ONE,
BABY, YOU THE ONLY ONE ¶
¶ YOU'RE, YOU'RE ALL
I'M LIVING FOR ¶
¶ YOUR LOVE I'LL KEEP
FOREVERMORE ¶
¶ YOU'RE THE FIRST ¶
¶ YOU'RE THE LAST ¶
¶ MY EVERYTHING ¶
[TIRES SCREECH]
OH, SHIT!
¶ WHOO ¶
¶ WHOO-HOO-OOH ¶
GO, MAN, GO!
¶ NA NA NA ¶
WHAT YOU GOT?
DODGERS TICKETS,
LAKERS TICKETS,
AND PHANTOM OF
THE OPERA TICKETS.
PHANTOM OF THE OPERA?
YEAH.
IT'S THEATER, MAN.
YOU EVER BEEN
TO THE THEATER?
WHAT THE HELL
WRONG WITH YOU, MAN?
DON'T NOBODY GIVE A DAMN
ABOUT NO PHANTOM OF THE OPERA.
HEY, FRANKLIN, THERE'S
MONEY IN CULTURE.
MAN, LET ME TELL YOU
SOMETHING, ROLAND.
BLACK PEOPLE DON'T WANT
TO SEE THAT SHIT.
NOW, I TOLD YOU TO GET ME
SOME GOOD SHIT
LIKE LUTHER VANDROSS TICKETS
OR SOMETHING.
LUTHER VANDROSS
IS NOT CULTURE.
FUCK CULTURE!
GET ME SOME GOOD SHIT.
PEOPLE COMPLAIN ABOUT
THESE FUCKED UP TICKETS.
YOU'RE MAKING ME
LOOK BAD, MAN.
OH, REALLY?
I'M SERIOUS.
NEXT TIME, MAN,
COME UP WITH SOME
BETTER STUFF.
OK.
GONNA STOP FUCKING
WITH YOU, ROLAND.
I'M FOR REAL!
YOU OWE ME, MAN.
I DON'T OWE YOU SHIT.
YOU OWE ME, FRANKLIN.
¶ I KNOW ¶
¶ THERE'S ONLY ¶
¶ ONLY ONE LIKE YOU ¶
¶ THERE'S NO WAY ¶
¶ THEY COULD HAVE MADE 2 ¶
¶ YOU'RE, YOU'RE ALL
I'M LIVING FOR ¶
¶ YOUR LOVE I'LL KEEP
FOREVERMORE ¶
¶ YOU'RE THE FIRST ¶
¶ YOU'RE THE LAST ¶
¶ MY EVERYTHING ¶
WHERE THE HELL
HAVE YOU BEEN?
YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO WASH IT,
NOT TAKE IT FOR A JOYRIDE.
MAN, WHERE YOU BEEN?
I BEEN LOOKING FOR YOU.
I BEEN TRYING
TO FIND YOU.
WHAT?
I'VE BEEN RIDING AROUND
LOOKING FOR YOU.
COME HERE. I'M GLAD
I FOUND YOU, MAN.
GET THE HELL ON.
THAT'S HIM. LET'S DO THIS.
¶ CAR WASH ¶
I NEED 2 ON THE FLOOR.
I NEED $200.
COME ON, COME ON.
UH-UH.
SAME TIME, MAN.
I DON'T KNOW YOU.
SAME TIME.
WILLIE.
YEAH? ALL RIGHTY, NOW.
GET OUT OF HERE. HURRY UP.
HEY, WHY DON'T Y'ALL TRY
TO HIDE SOME OF THIS SHIT?
KEEP IT ON THE DOWN-LOW.
YOU'LL GET A NIGGER BUSTED.
COME ON, MAN.
GET ME LOCKED UP AND SHIT.
HURRY UP.
HOW WE DOING?
WHAT'S UP, MAN?
WHAT YOU NEED?
OH, HOLD ON.
LET ME GUESS.
2 TO THE PHANTOM
OF THE OPERA, RIGHT?
I'VE ALREADY SEEN IT,
THANKS.
HOLD UP, MAN.
WAIT A MINUTE.
YOU THAT
SILLY ASS REPORTER
FROM THE CHANNEL 5 NEWS,
AIN'T YOU?
CHANNEL 12, ACTUALLY.
I KNEW IT.
WHAT'S UP, MAN?
JAMES RUSSELL.
HOW YOU DOING?
ALL RIGHT. WHAT'S UP?
WONDER IF WE
COULD TALK TO YOU
FOR A COUPLE OF SECONDS
ON CAMERA.
COOL.
JULIO,
IS THAT ALL RIGHT?
WHATEVER YOU WANT
TO DO, MAN.
LET'S ROLL IT.
SPEED.
WAIT A MINUTE,
WAIT A MINUTE. HOLD UP.
CUT.
LET ME STRAIGHTEN OUT
MY SHIT, MAN.
ALL RIGHT, I'M READY.
COOL. LET'S GO.
YOU'RE READY?
COOL.
YOU SURE?
I'M SURE.
OK.
SPEED.
THIS IS JAMES RUSSELL
REPORTING ON OUR CITY
AND HER CRIMES.
I'M HERE
AT A LOCAL CAR WASH
TALKING TO
THE CAR WASH HUSTLER.
YOU'VE GOT QUITE
AN OPERATION
SET UP HERE
FOR YOURSELF.
TELL ME, WHAT IS
GOING ON DOWN HERE?
I'M A BUSINESSMAN, MAN.
WHAT THE FUCK YOU THINK
GOIN' ON?
CUT, CUT, CUT.
Cameraman:
THAT'S A CUT.
WHAT?
YOU CAN'T USE THAT KIND
OF LANGUAGE ON TV.
WHAT LANGUAGE?
WHAT YOU TALKING ABOUT?
"FUCK."
"FUCK" WHAT?
YOU CANNOT SAY FUCK
ON TELEVISION.
FUCK THAT. YOU THE ONE
THAT CAME OVER HERE
AND WANTED ME TO DO
AN INTERVIEW.
DON'T TELL ME HOW TO TALK.
YOU NEED TO HURRY UP.
I GOT SHIT TO DO.
WELL, I GOT SHIT TO DO
ALSO, ALL RIGHT?
WELL, COME ON, MAN,
HURRY UP.
OK.
GET ON WITH IT, MAN.
SPEED.
THIS IS JAMES RUSSELL
REPORTING ON OUR CITY--
HEY, FRANKLIN.
HEY, WHAT'S UP, MAN?
I GOTTA GO, MAN.
Y'ALL DO A COMMERCIAL
OR FIND SOMEBODY ELSE.
WHAT UP, CARMINE?
CARMINE.
WHAT'S UP, MAN? I AIN'T
SEEN YOU IN A LONG TIME.
CUT.
FUCKING CUT!
WHEN AM I GONNA GET
MY MONEY, FRANKLIN?
WHAT MONEY?
OH, WAIT A MINUTE.
YOU'RE TALKING
ABOUT THE MONEY.
THE MONEY
THAT I OWE YOU.
I'M GONNA
PAY YOU, MAN.
LOOK AT ME, MAN.
YOU KNOW
I'M GONNA PAY YOU.
AND I GOT
YOUR PHONE CALLS.
WHEN YOU CALL,
EVERY TIME YOU CALL--
SOMEBODY STOLE MY PHONE.
STOLE MY GODDAMN PHONE.
CAN YOU BELIEVE
THAT SHIT?
I DON'T LIKE BROTHERS,
AND I DON'T LIKE WELCHERS.
KILLING YOU
WILL BE DOUBLE FUN.
COME ON, MAN.
STOP PLAYING.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING
ABOUT KILLING FOR?
IF YOU KILL ME,
HOW AM I GONNA PAY YOU?
OPEN THE DOOR
AND GET OUT OF MY CAR.
GET ON THE STREET
AND GET MY MONEY.
I'M GONNA GET IT,
BUT I DON'T WANT
TO LEAVE YOU MAD.
GIVE ME A HUG
OR SOMETHING.
GET OUT.
A KISS? OK.
FRANKLIN HATCHETT?
OH, HE DEAD, MAN.
THEY BURIED HIM DOWN
AT THE COMPTON CEMETERY.
YOU'RE UNDER ARREST.
HEY, WHAT THE FUCK
Y'ALL DOING, MAN?
I DIDN'T DO SHIT, MAN!
YEAH, NOBODY EVER DOES.
YOU HAVE THE RIGHT
TO REMAIN SILENT.
HEY, MAN, WAIT A MINUTE.
I'LL GIVE YOU $5.00
TO LET ME OUT.
OH, BRIBERY, TOO?
IN THE CAR.
WATCH MY HEAD,
WATCH MY HEAD.
AAH!
$5.00.
HE OFFERED ME $5.00.
HEY, MAN!
CHANNEL 5, HELP
A BROTHER OUT, MAN?
HEY, GERALDO!
OH, YOU AIN'T
GONNA DO NOTHING?
I'M GONNA GET YOUR ASS!
A SERIOUS CRIME.
JUSTIFIED PUNISHMENT.
THIS IS JAMES RUSSELL
REPORTING.
CHANNEL 12 NEWS.
WE GOT HIM.
WE DIDN'T GET SHIT.
LET'S GET OUT OF HERE.
MAN, I AM DEAD SERIOUS.
THE PO-PO TRIPPIN' NOW,
EVER SINCE
THAT O.J. SHIT, MAN.
I WAS JUST ROLLING
DOWN THE STREET,
WASN'T DOING NOTHING.
THEY GONNA PULL ME OVER, MAN.
I'M SERIOUS. I WAS JUST
LIVING GHETTO FABULOUS.
I HAD 5 OF MY
FINEST HOS--
ARE YOU HOT?
I'M A LITTLE HOT, MAN,
BUT I WAS JUST CHILLIN', MAN.
THE COP GONNA COME UP,
PULL BEHIND ME.
HE HAD THE LIGHTS
AND EVERYTHING.
"GET OUT OF THE CAR,
GET OUT OF THE CAR."
I AIN'T GETTIN' OUT THE CAR.
YEAH, I WAS LIKE, "NO,
I AIN'T GETTIN' OUT THE CAR."
THEN ALL MY HOS IN THE CAR,
THEY WAS SCARED.
THEY WAS LIKE,
"FRANKLIN, WE SCARED."
THEY BE SAYING
STUFF LIKE THAT.
I WAS LIKE, "NO, NO, NO.
I AIN'T STOPPING
'CAUSE I AIN'T DO NOTHING."
AND HE CAME UP TO THE CAR
AND SAID, "GET OUT THE CAR."
I GOT OUT OF THE CAR AND SAID,
"WHAT YOU CALLING BACKUP FOR?
THIS IS BETWEEN ME AND YOU.
I AIN'T EVEN DO NOTHING."
THEY GOT MY LICENSE,
MY REGISTRATION, EVERYTHING.
WHAT'S UP NOW?
YOU GOTTA TALK
TO 'EM LIKE THAT.
THEN HE STARTS--
STOP PLAYING, MAN.
THEN HE STARTED TRIPPIN'.
THAT'S WHEN
I SLAPPED HIM. UHH!
AND I TOOK HIS HANDCUFFS
AND PUT HIS HANDCUFFS ON HIM.
PUT HIM IN THE BACK SEAT
OF MY CAR AND SAID,
"I'M GONNA TAKE
YOUR ASS TO JAIL,
"'CAUSE YOU'RE THE ONE TRIPPIN'
AROUND HERE. YOU UNDERSTAND?
THEY PUT THEIR HANDS
ON YOU?
YEAH, THEY TRIED TO, MAN.
ONE DUDE TRIED TO GRAB ME
FROM THE BACK.
THAT'S HOW THEY CAUGHT ME.
FROM THE BACK?
HOW THEY DO IT?
THEY TRIED TO GRAB ME
LIKE THIS, JACK ME UP, MAN.
LIKE THAT?
NO. THEY WAS,
LIKE, GRABBING.
THEY WAS TRIPPIN'.
YEAH, LIKE THAT.
YEAH. YEAH.
MAN, GET THE HELL
OFF ME, MAN!
HEY!
WHERE'S YOUR SHIRT AT?
Man: GOOD-BYE,
SWEETNESS.
WHERE WE GOING, MAN?
JUST LEAVE ME
THE FUCK ALONE.
MAN, WHO YOU TALKING TO?
[SPEAKS FRENCH]
WHAT?
WELL VACU FELA
CULAY YOU,
JERRY-LEWIS-LIKING
MOTHERFUCKER, YOU.
[BUZZER]
Guard: LET'S MOVE IT.
HEY, MAN, LET ME
BORROW YOUR GUN.
COME ON BACK TO THE BACK
OF THE BUS, MAN.
YOU SHUT UP,
AND YOU SIT DOWN.
[SPEAKS FRENCH]
HUH?!
MAN, WHAT THE HELL
WRONG WITH YOU?
I DON'T PLAY THAT SHIT, MAN.
YOU BETTER CHECK
MY POLICE RECORD.
YOU DON'T KNOW
WHO YOU'RE MESSIN' WITH.
HUH?
YOU BETTER COME ON TO THE BACK
BEFORE YOU GET HURT.
PLAY THAT SHIT.
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
WAIT TILL WE
GET OFF THE BUS.
YEAH.
YEAH, YOU WAIT TILL WE
GET OFF THE BUS.
I'M GONNA KICK
YOUR ASS!
SHUT UP!
WHERE YOU FROM, HUH?
THAT FRENCH PART
OF COMPTON?
WHAT'S THAT YOU CLAIMING?
YOU DON'T KNOW WHO
YOU'RE MESSING WITH, MAN.
I'M DEEP IN THE STREETS.
I SLAP PEOPLE FOR FUN.
[CUBAN ACCENT]
THAT'S WHAT I DO, MAN.
YOU WANT TO PLAY ROUGH?
HUH?
OK.
DON'T KNOW WHO
YOU'RE MESSING WITH, MAN.
I KILL FOR FUN.
[FRANKLIN IMITATING
MICHAEL JACKSON]
¶ EE OLLY MOO ¶
¶ A LUDA ¶
¶ FU LOOZA ¶
¶ BO LOODA ¶
¶ DOH WOO ¶
[HORNS HONKING]
[SPEAKING FRENCH]
MAN, I AIN'T SCARED
TO GO TO JAIL.
TAKE ME TO JAIL, MAN.
WOULD YOU SPEED UP, PLEASE?
SHIT. I WANT TO GO BACK.
ALL MY COUSINS,
EVERYBODY UP IN THERE.
I WANT TO SEE
ALL MY FRIENDS.
AAH!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING UP THERE?
HURRY!
COME ON.
YOU ALL RIGHT?
AH, DEBRAY.
LET'S GET OUT OF HERE.
YES.
QUICK, QUICK, QUICK.
NO TIME. WE'LL
TAKE HIM WITH US.
WE GOTTA GO TOGETHER.
WE'RE A TEAM.
MOVE!
ALL RIGHT,
ALL RIGHT.
WE MADE IT, MAN.
WE DID IT.
EVERYBODY OK?
IS EVERYBODY ALL RIGHT?
HEY, HEY, HOMEY.
HEY, DAWG,
WHAT IT IS?
Y'ALL CAN DROP ME OFF
RIGHT OVER THERE, MAN.
MY COUSIN'S HOUSE
COMING UP.
Y'ALL CAN HOVER OVER THE ROOF.
Y'ALL DON'T EVEN
HAVE TO STOP, MAN.
Y'ALL CAN DROP ME OFF.
I CAN BE OUT OF HERE, MAN.
I KNOW Y'ALL PROBABLY
GOT SHIT TO DO--
SHUT THE FUCK UP!
COME ON, MAN. YOU CAN
DROP A BROTHER OFF.
Y'ALL DON'T NEED ME NO MORE.
COME ON, MAN.
[SPEAKING FRENCH]
15 MILLION.
15 MILLION?
$15 MILLION?
Y'ALL GOTTA CUT A BROTHER IN
ON THAT, MAN.
LET ME BE DOWN, MAN.
WE'LL SPLIT IT 3 WAYS.
7 FOR ME, 7 FOR YOU,
AND YOU GET WHATEVER'S
LEFT OVER, MAN,
'CAUSE YOU BEEN TRIPPIN'
EVER SINCE I MET YOU.
WHAT? WAIT A MINUTE.
WHAT YOU DOING WITH THE AX?
HEY, FORGET ABOUT
WHAT I SAID.
HEY, I DON'T KNOW SHIT ABOUT
NO $15 MILLION IN NO JAGUAR.
FORGET ABOUT THAT SHIT.
I DON'T EVEN KNOW WHERE WE AT.
I GOT A BAD MEMORY.
HOW'D WE GET UP HERE?
BE STILL.
I'M BEING STILL,
BUT PUT THE AX DOWN.
DON'T MOVE.
PARLEZ-VOUS, OUI, OUI.
AAH!
WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU?
TRYING TO CUT A BROTHER'S
HAND OFF, MAN.
DEBRAY, LA PORT.
ALWAYS TRYING
TO KILL SOMEBODY.
WHY DON'T YOU TRY
LOVING SOMEBODY?
HOLD UP, MAN.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
WHAT DID YOU OPEN
THE DOOR FOR?
OH, SHIT, MAN.
HEY, LOOK,
Y'ALL TRIPPIN'.
WAIT A MINUTE. Y'ALL
WANT SOME GIRLS?
I CAN GET YOU ANY KIND
OF GIRL YOU WANT, MAN.
BLACK, JAPANESE.
LOOK, HEY, I CAN TAKE YOU
OVER TO MY GRANDMAMA HOUSE.
SHE COOK YOU SOME CHICKEN,
SOME CORNBREAD, SOME GOULET.
AAAAAHHHHHHH!
SHIT!
AAH!
IT'S COLD.
IT'S COLDER THAN
A MOTHERFUCKER.
A SERIOUS CRIME.
JUSTIFIED PUNISHMENT.
THIS IS JAMES RUSSELL
REPORTING.
THAT'S SOME HARD-HITTING
STUFF, RUSSELL.
JOHN TESH
SCHOOL OF JOURNALISM.
COME ON, BARCLAY.
JUST WATCH IT ONE MORE TIME
BEFORE YOU DECIDE--
WHY SHOULD I?
NOBODY ELSE WILL.
WHO GIVES A RAT'S ASS
ABOUT SOME 2-BIT
HUSTLER?
THE PEOPLE GETTING RIPPED OFF
BY THIS 2-BIT HUSTLER
GIVE A RAT'S ASS.
YOU'RE JUST ANOTHER
WALKING HEAD SHOT,
AREN'T YOU?
ANOTHER PRETTY BOY
WANKER
MASQUERADING
AS A REPORTER.
I DON'T NEED THIS.
I DON'T NEED THIS BULLSHIT.
OK, WELL, THIS
IS THE SKINNY, MATE.
YOU'RE FIRED.
HAVE YOUR STUFF OUT
BY MONDAY.
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
BARCLAY. BE BRIEF.
WHAT PART
OF "YOU'RE FIRED"
DON'T YOU UNDERSTAND?
NO, NOT YOU,
YOU ASSHOLE.
I'M TALKING
TO SOMEBODY ELSE.
WHAT?
Man: TRAGEDY AND TERROR
STRIKE THE SOUTHLAND.
GOOD AFTERNOON.
A BUS DELIVERING PRISONERS
FROM THE MEN'S CENTRAL LOCKUP
TO THE VAN NUYS COURTHOUSE
WAS DESTROYED
JUST MOMENTS AGO
ON THE FIRST STREET BRIDGE
IN DOWNTOWN LOS ANGELES.
14 PRISONERS AND 2 POLICEMEN
WERE KILLED
[BELL RINGS]
IN WHAT AUTHORITIES
ARE DESCRIBING
AS A COMMANDO-STYLE RAID.
ALL BODIES
HAVE BEEN ACCOUNTED FOR
WITH THE EXCEPTION
OF 2 PRISONERS.
WITNESSES SAY THEY SAW 2 MEN
BOARDING A HELICOPTER
SHORTLY AFTER THE BUS
EXPLODED INTO FLAMES.
THE 2 FUGITIVES ARE WANTED
IN CONNECTION
WITH THE MURDERS.
MAN, THIS HAS GOT SWEEPS WEEK
WRITTEN ALL OVER IT.
YEAH.
LET ME KNOW
HOW IT TURNS OUT.
...APPREHENDING
THESE 2 MEN.
PICTURED ON THE LEFT
IS A JOHN DOE
POLICE ARRESTED EARLIER
AT L.A.X.
FOR POSSESSION
OF A COUNTERFEIT PASSPORT.
AND ON THE RIGHT,
FRANKLIN MAURICE HATCHETT,
A LOCAL STREET HUSTLER
WITH SUSPECTED GANG TIES
WHO WAS EN ROUTE
TO VAN NUYS
TO BE ARRAIGNED ON CHARGES
OF SOLICITING GOODS.
THE 2 FUGITIVES,
JOHN DOE AND HATCHETT,
ARE CONSIDERED DANGEROUS.
14 PRISONERS DUE TO FACE
A VAN NUYS JUDGE TODAY
NOW FACE THE ULTIMATE
JUDGMENT DAY OF ALL.
ONE WHERE SENTENCING COMES
WITH NO CHANCE OF REVERSAL.
FREEZE!
Cop: COME OUT WITH YOUR
HANDS ABOVE YOUR HEAD.
Franklin: I'M GONNA COME OUT,
BUT I DIDN'T DO IT!
DON'T SHOOT!
I DIDN'T KILL NO COPS!
[HORNS HONKING]
Russell: HELLO.
IS THIS JAMES RUSSELL?
I'M ON MY WAY.
I CANNOT WAIT FOR YOU
TO EAT MY ASS.
ALL RIGHT, HERE IT IS.
YEAH?
GOOD AFTERNOON.
I'M DETECTIVE PICKETT,
AND THIS
IS WILLIAMS HERE.
I WONDERED IF WE MIGHT
HAVE A LITTLE CHAT
WITH YOU
ABOUT FRANKLIN HATCHETT.
WELL, FRANKLIN'S
NOT HERE, OK?
WE'RE DEALING WITH
A MULTIPLE HOMICIDE HERE.
WOULD YOU JUST
OPEN THE DOOR?
EXCUSE YOU?
I'M SORRY. LISTEN,
IT WOULD ONLY TAKE
A FEW MINUTES OF YOUR TIME.
WE'D REALLY APPRECIATE IT.
PLEASE.
YEAH, ALL RIGHT.
COME ON.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
SO, UH, WHEN WAS THE LAST TIME
YOU SPOKE TO HIM?
WHO, FRANKLIN?
YEAH.
WELL, HE LEFT
ON THE FREAK TRAIN
TO ATLANTA
6 WEEKS AGO.
YOU KNOW, I HAVEN'T
SEEN HIM SINCE.
WHAT, DO YOU THINK
THIS IS FUNNY?
YOU THINK THIS IS A JOKE?
I GOT A BUSLOAD OF BODIES
AND A COUPLE DEAD COPS
BECAUSE OF YOUR GANGBANGER.
LOOK, FRANKLIN
AIN'T NO BANGER, OK?
IF I FIND OUT
YOU'RE HELPING HIM,
I'M TELLING YOU RIGHT NOW,
I SWEAR TO GOD I'M GOING
TO MAKE YOUR LIFE MISERABLE.
HEY, HEY, HEY,
BACK OFF, PLEASE.
WILL YOU TREAT THE LADY
WITH SOME RESPECT?
THANK YOU.
CAN YOU HELP US OUT, PAULA?
I SWEAR, I DON'T KNOW
WHERE HE IS, OK?
OH, THIS IS SUCH
BULLSHIT!
YOU KNOW...
HEY, IT'S OK, IT'S OK.
ALL I'M SAYING IS IF HE
TRIES TO CONTACT YOU,
GIVE ME A CALL, ALL RIGHT?
IT'S SO MUCH BETTER FOR FRANKLIN
IF HE TURNS HIMSELF IN.
HE STAYS OUT
ON THE STREET, PAULA,
HE'S GONNA
GET HIMSELF KILLED.
NOW, I'M TRYING
TO PROTECT HIM, I REALLY AM.
THIS IS MY CARD.
WILL YOU GIVE ME A HOLLER?
YEAH, OK.
THANK YOU.
KEEP IT RUNNING.
OK.
THIS MIGHT BE QUICK.
ALL RIGHT.
WHITE BOY.
WHAT THE FUCK WAS THAT FOR?
THAT'S FOR GETTING ME
BUSTED, GODDAMN IT.
WHAT YOU BRING A GUN
DOWN HERE FOR?
'CAUSE YOU'RE WANTED
FOR MURDER, ASSHOLE.
I AIN'T MURDERED
NO-GODDAMN-BODY.
I DON'T KNOW THAT.
WELL, NOW YOU KNOW,
'CAUSE IF I COULD,
I'D MURDER YOUR ASS
RIGHT NOW,
COMING DOWN HERE
WITH A GUN AND SHIT.
YOU KNOW,
GUNS DON'T KILL PEOPLE.
STUPID MOTHERFUCKERS
WITH GUNS KILL PEOPLE.
OH, I'M ENLIGHTENED.
YEAH. LET ME ENLIGHTEN
YOUR ASS.
BRING YOUR MONKEY ASS
ON UP HERE.
GOT ME RUNNING
ALL OVER GODDAMN TOWN.
PEOPLE SHOOTING AT ME
AND SHIT.
YOU THE ONE
GOT ME IN THIS SHIT.
OUGHT TO KICK YOUR ASS
IN THE HEAD.
FREEZING.
I KNOW. I WAS IN THE
MOTHERFUCKER EARLIER.
LISTEN TO ME.
I WANT AN EXCLUSIVE.
A WHAT?
RIGHT NOW THE ENTIRE CITY
IS LOOKING FOR YOUR ASS.
THE COPS WANT PAYBACK
FOR MURDERED COPS.
HOW MANY TIMES
I GOT TO TELL YOU
I DIDN'T KILL
NO-GODDAMN-BODY?
REGARDLESS,
THEY WANT YOUR ASS DEAD.
FRANKLIN,
I WILL PROTECT YOU.
I'LL GET YOU TURNED IN
SAFE AND SOUND,
LET YOU TELL YOUR SIDE
OF THE STORY,
BUT I WANT THE EXCLUSIVE.
I'LL HIDE YOU
FOR THE WEEKEND.
IT'LL ALL BE OVER
ON MONDAY.
FIRST OF ALL,
I DON'T TRUST YOUR ASS,
AND HOW THE HELL I KNOW
THIS EXCLUSIVE SHIT
GONNA CLEAR MY NAME?
I GUESS YOU DON'T.
BUT WITHOUT ME, YOU'RE
PROBABLY GONNA END UP DEAD.
THEY NEED SOMEONE TO BLAME,
AND GUESS WHAT.
RIGHT NOW IT'S YOU.
WHAT DO YOU SAY?
I AIN'T STAYING IN THIS
NEIGHBORHOOD, MAN.
I CAN'T STAY HERE FOR
NO 2 DAYS. I'M SORRY.
THAT'S RIGHT. YOU CAN'T
STAY HERE FOR NO 2 DAYS.
WHAT YOU TALKIN' ABOUT?
YOU'RE COMING
TO MY WEDDING.
YOUR WEDDING?
SHIT, HELL, NO.
I AIN'T GOING
NOWHERE.
PO-PO LOOKING
FOR ME, MAN.
TRYING TO KILL ME?
UH-UH.
STAYING
ON THE LOW-LOW.
GODDAMN.
HOW YOU DO THAT?
DID A REPORT ONCE
ON ESCAPE ARTISTS...
AND THE WOMEN WHO LOVE THEM.
TEACH ME HOW TO DO
THAT SHIT REAL QUICK.
THERE'S NO TIME.
COME ON.
COME ON, DAWG,
WE GOT TIME.
I NEED YOU TO TAKE A SHOWER,
SHAVE THE BEARD,
LOSE THE EARRING,
AND PLEASE DO SOMETHING
ABOUT THAT HAIR
OF YOURS.
WHAT YOU TALKIN' ABOUT?
MY 'DO IS TIGHT.
EVERY COP IN THE CITY
IS LOOKING FOR THAT TIGHT 'DO.
WHATEVER, MAN. LOOK,
I'LL HOOK UP THE HAIR,
BUT I AIN'T TOUCHING
THE EARRING,
'CAUSE I'M STILL
A PLAYER!
THAT'S FINE.
I'M GONNA MAKE A PHONE CALL.
I DON'T THINK THERE'S ANY
HOT WATER LEFT.
WHAT?
YOU HEARD ME.
WHAT?!
PUNK-ASS WHITE BOY.
THIS TUB BETTER BE CLEAN.
[DOOR SLAMS]
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
YEAH. WHO IS IT?
HEY, BARCLAY, IT'S JAMES.
HOW YOU DOING?
LISTEN TO ME.
I GOT FRANKLIN HATCHETT.
RUSSELL, DON'T PLAY
GAMES WITH ME.
WORDS LIKE THAT
GIVE ME A STIFFY,
AND AT MY AGE, I CAN'T
AFFORD TO WASTE THEM.
I'M NOT KIDDING YOU.
HE'S AT MY PLACE RIGHT NOW
SAFE AND SOUND
FOR THE MOMENT.
CONGRATULATIONS,
YOU'RE REHIRED.
I THOUGHT I WAS SUPPOSED TO
CLEAR OUT MY STUFF BY MONDAY.
DIDN'T YOU SAY THAT?
YOU SAID THAT, RIGHT?
NO, BUT, JIMMY, DARLING,
YOU DIDN'T REALLY TAKE
ME SERIOUSLY, DID YOU?
YOU'RE PULITZER MATERIAL.
I'VE ALWAYS SAID THAT.
I'LL SEND A CAMERA CREW
DOWN TO--WHAT IS IT--
THE 20th PRECINCT
IN, SAY, AN HOUR?
NOT A CHANCE. I'M GOING TO
KEEP HIM ON ICE UNTIL MONDAY.
FOR SWEEPS WEEK.
NO, NO, DON'T BE
FOOLISH, JIMMY.
A BIRD IN THE HAND
IS WORTH A 10-SHARE
FOR THE WHOLE WEEKEND.
[CHUCKLING]
HEY, BARCLAY, FUCK YOU.
THIS IS MY STORY,
AND YOU KNOW IT.
YOU'RE QUITE RIGHT.
MONDAY IT IS.
TA-TA.
LOSER.
FREEZE!
TV: VIC DAMONE...
FREEZE! GET YOUR
GODDAMN HANDS ON THE CAR!
TV: VIC DAMONE...
HIS MUSIC
WILL LAST FOREVER.
WHAT THE HELL
IS A VIC DAMONE?
TV: VIC DAMONE'S
GREATEST HITS...
AIN'T NO GODDAMN GREATEST HIT.
I AIN'T NEVER HEARD IT.
HE THRILLED THE WORLD
WHEN HE MARRIED
ACTRESS DIAHANN CARROLL.
NOW HE'LL
THRILL YOU AGAIN...
HOW THE HELL
AN ITALIAN GONNA GET
A FINE-ASS BLACK WOMAN
LIKE THAT?
THE TIMELESS HITS
OF VIC DAMONE.
"VIC DAMONE."
SHIT, HE CAN'T SING.
ONLY REASON SHE MARRIED HIM
'CAUSE HE GOT MONEY.
TAKIN' ALL OUR SISTERS.
I'M JAMES RUSSELL.
THOSE STORIES ALONG
WITH ANDY ROONEY
TONIGHT ON
60 MINUTES.
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
HELLO?
HONEY?
SWEETHEART,
I'M OUT THE DOOR.
PEOPLE ARE
ALREADY SHOWING UP.
I AM SO SORRY. SOMETHING
REALLY IMPORTANT CAME UP.
MORE IMPORTANT THAN
OUR REHEARSAL DINNER?
OF COURSE NOT.
AND--AND I'M BRINGING
SOMEBODY WITH ME.
WHO?
OLD, DEAR FRIEND OF MINE
FROM COLLEGE.
JUST KIND OF RAN
INTO HIM TODAY.
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
YOU SOUND FUNNY.
I'M PERFECT. GREAT.
I AM EXCELLENT.
I'LL SEE YOU BEFORE
YOU KNOW IT. I LOVE YOU.
I LOVE YOU, TOO.
HURRY UP.
[SIGHS] FUCK ME.
HEY, FRANKLIN,
I'M GONNA START THE CAR.
I'LL MEET YOU IN
THE COURTYARD, ALL RIGHT?
KISS MY ASS!
FIND SOMETHING
IN THE CLOSET THAT FITS
AND MOVE YOUR ASS!
WE'RE LATE!
AND THIS TOWEL
WEREN'T CLEAN,
YOU DIRTY ASS WHITE BOY!
YOU HAD TO PICK THAT ONE,
DIDN'T YOU?
THIS YOUR RIDE,
MAN?
YES, AND THAT'S MY FAVORITE
FUCKING SUIT YOU'RE WEARING.
I LOOK GOOD, DON'T I?
DON'T GET MAD AT ME
'CAUSE I LOOK BETTER
THAN YOU IN YOUR OWN SHIT.
I SHOULD BE EBONY
MAN OF THE MONTH.
IS THIS SOMETHING
TO BE PROUD OF?
YOU WOULDN'T KNOW NOTHIN'
ABOUT THAT WITH YOUR GOOFY ASS.
YOU FUCK UP THE SUIT,
AND WE GOT A PROBLEM.
FUCK THE SUIT. WE
ALREADY GOT A PROBLEM.
GODDAMN!
LOOK AT THIS SHIT!
JAMES RUSSELL, YOU HUSTLIN'
SON OF A BITCH.
YEAH,
LOOK WHO'S TALKING.
AT LEAST I'VE WORKED
FOR EVERYTHING I HAVE.
YEAH, YOU WORKED YOURSELF
RIGHT INTO SOME RICH PUSSY,
THAT'S WHAT YOU DID.
NO WONDER YOU DON'T GIVE
A DAMN IF I'M INNOCENT.
YOUR ASS GONNA GET
MARRIED AND RETIRE.
LET'S GET A COUPLE
THINGS STRAIGHT
ABOUT TONIGHT'S
DINNER, ALL RIGHT?
YOU DON'T SPEAK UNLESS
SPOKEN TO. NOT A WORD.
YOU STAY BY MY SIDE.
IF YOU TRY ANYTHING
FUCKED UP OR FUNNY,
I SWEAR TO GOD,
I WILL KILL YOU MYSELF.
JUST LIKE YOU DID
BACK ON THE DOCKS?
HA HA!
I WILL BEAT YOUR ASS.
YOU AIN'T
BEATIN' SHIT, HOMES.
I'LL BEAT YOUR ASS.
SHIT.
ALL RIGHT. YOU WENT TO
STANFORD, WHICH IS WHERE?
HOW THE HELL
I SUPPOSED TO KNOW?
IT'S IN THE BAY AREA, WHERE YOU
GRADUATED WITH HONORS IN '88.
AND YOUR NAME--
YOUR NAME TONIGHT...
IS JONATHAN...SMITH.
FUCK THE JONATHAN SMITH.
I'M ME.
ONE MORE THING.
DO NOT SAY A WORD ABOUT
MY FIANCéE'S WEIGHT.
SHE'S VERY SENSITIVE
ABOUT THAT.
MAN, YOU MUST HAVE ONE
OF THEM FAT-ASSED
TACO BELL, McDONALD-EATIN',
BIG-BOOTY-ASSED--
JIMMY!
MR. CIPRIANI.
HEY, HOW ARE YOU?
HOW MANY TIMES I GOT TO
TELL YOU? CALL ME DAD.
YOU'RE NOT GETTING
NERVOUS, ARE YOU?
WHO WOULDN'T BE?
YEAH, THAT'S TRUE.
WHO'S THIS?
THIS IS A VERY GOOD
FRIEND OF MINE. THIS IS--
VIC DAMONE.
JUNIOR.
OH, YEAH.
SO HE'S DIAHANN CARROLL'S KID
AND VIC DAMONE'S KID.
SO YOU'RE HALF...
AND HALF ITALIAN.
HEY, PAISAN.
HEY, ME AND YOUR FATHER?
FORGET ABOUT IT. COME HERE.
MAMMA MIA!
GOD, YOUR HOUSE...
MAGNIFICO!
MOLTA BELLA!
TUTTI FRUTTI!
WHERE'D YOU LEARN
HOW TO TALK ITALIAN?
VIC TALK TO YOU IN ITALIAN
WHEN YOU WERE A KID?
ALL THE TIME.
HERE SHE IS!
JAMES, IT'S NICE
OF YOU TO SHOW UP.
HONEY, I'M
TERRIBLY SORRY.
FIANCéE GRACE,
THIS IS MY FRIEND VIC.
YOU'RE PHAT.
PHAT. DAMN!
PHAT.
P-H-A-T. PRETTY HOT
AND TEMPTING.
I'M STUNNED
BY YOUR PHATNESS.
JAMES, YOU'RE
A LUCKY MAN TO HAVE
SUCH A PHAT-ASSED
FIANCéE, MAN.
SHE FINE.
THANKS.
YOU'RE WELCOME.
YOU MADE IT.
I THOUGHT YOU'D BE OFF
COVERING THAT PRISON ESCAPE
WITH THE REST OF THE
LOW-LIFE SENSATIONALISTS.
MOTHER,
GIVE IT A REST.
ACTUALLY, I AM COVERING THAT
SORT OF INDIRECTLY, MOM.
HOW MANY TIMES DO
I HAVE TO TELL YOU
TO CALL ME
MRS. CIPRIANI?
CONNIE, THIS
IS VIC DAMONE JR.
HE'S JIMMY'S
GOOD FRIEND.
WHY DON'T YOU TELL
US WHAT IT WAS LIKE
GROWING UP IN THAT
SHOW-BIZ ATMOSPHERE?
EVERYBODY'S
INTERESTED.
OH, WELL, YOU KNOW.
I HAD A LOT OF FRIENDS.
JUNIOR WALKER JR.,
SAMMY DAVIS JR. JR.
CALL ME ALL THE TIME,
WE HANG OUT ALL THE TIME.
AND WHAT DO YOU DO
NOW, MR. DAMONE JR.?
UH, I'M IN--
SALES.
RETAIL?
SEATS.
ON THE STOCK EXCHANGE.
BROKER?
TICKET SCALPER.
BUT I CAN GET YOU
ANYTHING YOU WANT
IF YOU LET ME
KNOW AHEAD OF TIME.
HE'S A FUNNY GUY.
HE'S HYSTERICAL.
KILLS ME.
ABOUT SOME NICE
DOM PéRIGNON '85?
HOW ABOUT
SOME COLT .45?
[CHUCKLING]
WOULD YOU EXCUSE ME
FOR ONE SECOND?
I NEED TO TALK TO YOU.
WHAT?
WHAT THE FUCK DO YOU
THINK YOU'RE DOING?
WHAT DO YOU
THINK I'M DOING?
I'M MINGLING
WITH THE RICH FOLKS.
I'M LOCKING YOUR ASS
IN THE FUCKING CLOSET
FOR THE REST
OF THE WEEKEND.
LOOK, MAN, DON'T
EVEN START WITH ME.
YOU THE ONE BROUGHT ME OUT HERE
ALL IN THE MIDDLE OF NOWHERE
IN BEVERLY HILLS MINGLING
WITH THESE UPPITY-ASS PEOPLE.
I'M WANTED FOR MURDER,
AND MY LIFE ON THE LINE--
WHAT ABOUT MY LIFE?
WHAT ABOUT MY LIFE, HUH?
I'M LOOKIN'
AT YOUR LIFE.
GRACE! COME HERE,
GIRL. WHAT'S UP?
THIS IS BEAUTIFUL.
I COULDN'T BE HAPPIER
FOR YOU AND JAMES.
IT'S ABOUT TIME
HE SETTLED DOWN
AFTER ALL THE WOMEN
HE BEEN THROUGH.
AND THOSE 2 TWINS
IN SCHOOL WASN'T HIS.
MM-MMM.
THAT WAS ALL A LIE.
HE HAD A LOT OF WOMEN.
MATTER OF FACT,
HE HAD ALL THE WOMEN--
ALL THE WOMEN, ALL THE GUYS,
I FUCKED THEM ALL.
Guy: HERE WE GO.
I'D LIKE TO PROPOSE A TOAST,
IF YOU DON'T MIND.
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN!
EVERYBODY!
PROPOSE--PROPOSE A TOAST!
COME ON. THIS IS
VIC DAMONE'S SON.
JAMES...
IF YOU DON'T MIND.
GRACE...
YOU'RE JAMES' FIRST,
HIS LAST, HIS EVERYTHING,
AND YOU'RE THE ANSWER
TO ALL HIS DREAMS.
YOU'RE HIS SUN, HIS MOON,
HIS GUIDING STAR.
YOU'RE KIND OF WONDERFUL,
THAT'S WHAT YOU ARE.
HE KNOWS THERE'S
ONLY ONE OF YOU...
ISN'T THAT
BARRY WHITE?
THERE'S NO WAY
HE COULD HAVE MADE 2.
YOU'RE ALL HE'S LIVING FOR.
YOUR LOVE...
HE'LL KEEP FOREVERMORE.
YOU'RE HIS FIRST...
HIS LAST...
HIS EVERYTHING.
THAT WAS BEAUTIFUL.
I TRY TO DO WHAT I CAN DO
WHEN I CAN DO IT.
CONGRATULATIONS.
YOU GOT A PHONE?
OVER THERE.
THANK YOU.
YOU CAN SEE
THIS KID IS ITALIAN.
HE FEELS DEEP.
DEEP.
HELLO?
Woman: HELLO?
HEY, BABY, WHAT'S UP?
IT'S ME.
OH, NO, DON'T YOU
"BABY, IT'S ME" ME.
I JUST SAW YOUR ASS
ON THE NEWS
TALKING ABOUT YOU
KILLED SOME COP.
WHAT?!
I JUST SAW YOU
ON THE NEWS--
WHO TOLD YOU THAT? HELL, NO,
I DIDN'T KILL NOBODY!
YOU KILLED SOME COP!
HELL, NO!
ONCE AGAIN YOU ARE IN
TROUBLE FOR SOMETHING!
WHAT DID YOU DO ANYWAY?
DON'T YELL AT ME!
ARE YOU GONNA LET ME TALK?
WHAT?
WELL, LISTEN THEN,
GODDAMN IT!
STOP WATCHING
THE GODDAMN NEWS!
SOMEBODY SET ME UP!
WHERE HAVE YOU BEEN
FOR THE LAST 24 HOURS?
YOU BETTER NOT BE
OVER NO GIRL'S HOUSE!
HELL, NO, I AIN'T OVER AT
NO GODDAMN GIRL'S HOUSE!
I'M WANTED FOR MURDER! I AIN'T
GOT TIME TO GET NO PUSSY!
WHAT?!
I AIN'T FUCKIN'
NOBODY BUT YOU.
YEAH, UH-HUH.
WHAT ABOUT THIS GUY NAMED
CARMINE JUST CALLED HERE
SAYING HE'S GONNA KILL US
IF YOU DON'T GIVE HIM
$25,000, FRANKLIN?
WHAT?!
I DON'T OWE HIM
NO GODDAMN $25,000!
OK, WE GOT HIM.
HE'S CALLING FROM A 310
AREA CODE, A 274 PREFIX.
WHAT'S HE DOING
IN BEVERLY HILLS?
LOOK, JUST LOCK THE DOORS
AND DON'T ANSWER THE PHONE
AND GET UNDER THE BED!
I'M ON MY WAY, ALL RIGHT?
I'M ON MY WAY!
Woman:
GET UNDER THE--
VIC, YOU OK?
SOMEBODY BOTHERING YOU?
NAW. NAW,
EVERYTHING'S COOL.
FRANK SINATRA JR.
GOT IN TROUBLE AGAIN.
THEY GOT IT DOWN
TO A ONE BLOCK-RADIUS.
HE'S ON ROXBURY...
BETWEEN SUNSET
AND LEXINGTON.
RIGHT. THEY'RE
GONNA CHECK ON IT.
SHIT.
WHERE THE HELL DO YOU
THINK YOU'RE GOING?
I'M LEAVING, MAN.
I'M OUT.
YOU'RE OUT?
WHO'D YOU CALL,
FRANKLIN, YOUR PARTNER?
YOU CALLED YOUR PARTNER,
DIDN'T YOU?
PARTNER? WHAT THE HELL
YOU TALKIN' ABOUT?
LOOK, MAN,
I CALLED MY GIRL.
SHE'S PREGNANT, AND SHE
NEEDS ME, AND I'M OUT.
THAT IS NOT
PART OF OUR DEAL!
MAN, DAMN OUR DEAL!
I AIN'T DEALIN'
MY LIFE AWAY.
WHY YOU HUSTLING ME, HUH?
WHY YOU WON'T
JUST TURN ME IN, HUH?
WHAT YOU WAITIN' ON?
I THOUGHT SO.
THIS IS BULLSHIT.
YOU GOT ME RUNNING--
LOOK, I'M HELPING YOU.
YOU GOTTA HELP ME, TOO.
I NEED YOUR STORY
LIVE ON MONDAY.
IT'S SWEEPS WEEK, MAN.
SWEEPS WEEK?!
MAN, FUCK SWEEPS WEEK!
YOU GOT ME OUT HERE,
I'M WANTED FOR MURDER,
YOU TALKING ABOUT
A GODDAMN BROOM AND SHIT!
MAN, GET ME A TAXI!
[POLICE RADIO CRACKLES]
WHAT IS THIS SWEEPS
WEEK THING AGAIN?
BUT YOU DIDN'T TELL ME
WHERE YOU'RE GOING.
GRACE, GRACE,
YOU HAVE TO TRUST ME.
I'M ONTO SOMETHING BIG.
WHAT AM I GOING
TO TELL EVERYBODY?
YOU'LL THINK OF SOMETHING.
I'LL BE BACK FIRST THING
IN THE MORNING, I SWEAR.
JAMES...
I LOVE YOU.
I KNOW.
YOU BETTER NOT
BE LYING TO ME.
WHAT THE HELL I GOT
TO LIE TO YOU FOR?
I HAPPEN TO KNOW HOW
YOUR TYPE OPERATES.
MY TYPE?
YEAH.
SO WHY THE HELL
YOU TAKE MY TYPE
TO YOUR GODDAMN DINNER
REHEARSAL FOR A DAMN STORY?
I'M STUCK WITH YOU.
YOU AIN'T STUCK WITH SHIT.
I FIGURED YOUR WHITE ASS OUT.
OH, YOU HAVE?
YEAH. YOU'RE FULL OF SHIT.
YOU ONE DESPERATE-ASS
MIDDLE-CLASS WHITE BOY
THAT DON'T GIVE A DAMN WHO YOU
STEP ON TO GET WHAT YOU WANT.
THAT'S WHAT YOU ARE. YOU NEED TO
GET YOUR PRIORITIES STRAIGHT.
MY PRIORITIES?
YOUR GODDAMN
PRIORITIES.
I'M NOT THE ONE WANTED
FOR MURDER, REMEMBER?
LOOK, MAN, I'M SICK OF
YOUR SMART-ASS COMMENTS.
YOU KNOW I AIN'T
MURDERED NO-GODDAMN-BODY.
YOU THE REASON WHY I'M IN
THIS SHIT IN THE FIRST PLACE.
I WAS DOWN THERE MINDING
MY OWN GODDAMN BUSINESS,
LIVING GHETTO FABULOUS,
I WASN'T MESSIN' WITH NOBODY.
YOU CAME AND FUCKED THAT UP.
YOU KNOW HOW MUCH MONEY I WAS
MAKING DOWN AT THAT CAR WASH?
A BUCK, BUCK--2.98?
I WILL SLAP YOU, MAN.
I WILL SLAP THE HELL OUTTA YOU.
YOU DON'T PLAY WITH ME. YOU
DON'T KNOW WHO YOU MESSIN' WITH.
I DON'T EVEN KNOW WHEN
I'M GONNA SLAP SOMEBODY.
MY REFLEXES JUST SLAP PEOPLE.
I BE LIKE, "DAMN!
WHY DID I DO THAT?"
I DON'T KNOW WHEN I
BE SLAPPIN' PEOPLE.
YOU KEEP MESSIN' WITH ME.
I'M DANGEROUS.
I'M SCARED OF MYSELF.
THEY CALL ME "SNAP AND POP,"
'CAUSE I SNAP AND I WILL
POP YOUR ASS IN THE MOUTH.
DON'T MESS WITH ME, MAN.
BETTER WATCH YOUR BACK.
WATCH YOUR GODDAMN BACK.
EVEN IN THE SHOWER,
EATIN' AT PICNICS,
YOU BETTER WATCH YOUR
GODDAMN BACK. MAKE A RIGHT.
THERE'S MY CRIB
RIGHT THERE.
AND THERE GOES YOUR
STAKEOUT RIGHT THERE. SHIT!
QUICK, TURN DOWN HERE.
I KNOW A SHORTCUT.
ALL RIGHT...OHH!
SHE JUST TURNED
THE LIGHTS OUT.
YOU'RE UP, SPORT.
[SIGHS]
UNH!
SHIT!
GIRL, WHAT THE HELL IS
WRONG WITH YOU? IT'S ME!
DON'T TAKE THAT TONE WITH ME,
FRANKLIN MAURICE HATCHETT, OK?
SEE, I SHOULD CRACK YOUR
THICK-ASS SKULL RIGHT NOW.
WHAT YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
LEAVING ME HERE ALL ALONE!
IS THIS THE KIND OF FATHER
THAT YOU'RE GONNA BE?
NO, TELL ME RIGHT NOW.
I'LL MOVE BACK TO RIVERSIDE.
DON'T THINK THAT I WON'T.
WOULD YOU CALM DOWN?
WHAT'S UP WITH THE HAIR
AND THAT SUIT?
I MEAN, YOU LOOK LIKE YOU
JUST STEPPED OUT OF A CASKET!
CALM DOWN!
NOW, YOU KNOW I
AIN'T KILLED NOBODY.
IT'S ME, BABY. IT'S ME.
COME ON, NOW.
YOU KNOW I NEED YOU.
WHY YOU THINK I CAME
OVER HERE SO FAST?
I'M WORRIED ABOUT YOU.
ALL RIGHT.
I'M SORRY, OK?
YEAH.
YOU KNOW I LOVE YOU.
I'M SORRY, OK?
SHE JUST TURNED
THE LIGHTS BACK ON.
HUH? HUH?
BINGO. LET'S GO.
OK, BUT WHO IS THIS?
AND WHAT IS HE DOING HERE?
THAT'S--
JAMES RUSSELL,
CHANNEL 12 NEWS.
THE WEATHERMAN?
WHAT ARE YOU
DOING WITH HIM?
THAT'S--THAT'S
JUST MY WHITE FRIEND.
HE GONNA HELP ME
GET OUTTA THIS MESS.
BUT WHAT ABOUT CARMINE
AND THE MONEY
THAT YOU OWE HIM?
DON'T WORRY ABOUT THAT
'CAUSE HE'S LYIN'.
I DO NOT OWE HIM
NO $25,000!
I OWE HIM $7,000. HE ADDED ON
INTEREST. HE LYIN', BABY.
I DON'T EVEN
KNOW WHY I ASKED.
I'M SORRY, OK?
ALL RIGHT. CALM DOWN.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT,
OK? ALL RIGHT?
HOW YOU DOIN'?
I'M OK.
HOW THE BABY DOIN'?
HE FINE.
HOW MY BABY BOY DOIN'?
YOU AIN'T WORRYING ABOUT
NOTHIN'. I'M SERIOUS NOW.
MY BABY COME OUT WITH 2 TOES,
I'M GONNA KICK YOUR ASS.
YOU'VE HAD THE SONOGRAM,
I ASSUME.
WHAT?
SONOGRAM? DID A 3-PART
EXPOSé A FEW YEARS BACK
ON PRE-NATAL HEALTHCARE.
WE DISCOVERED
THAT NOT ONLY--
[POUNDING]
POLICE.
OPEN THE DOOR.
WE KNOW YOU'RE IN THERE,
HATCHETT.
IN A MINUTE!
SHH!
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT ELSE TO SAY.
SHH!
GIMME YOUR
PAGER NUMBER.
WHAT FOR?
JUST GIMME
YOUR PAGER NUMBER!
OPEN THIS
FUCKING DOOR,
OR WE'RE GONNA
BREAK IT IN!
ANYTHING GO WRONG,
YOU PAGE ME, OK?
YOU CAN REACH ME THERE.
EVERYTHING GONNA BE ALL RIGHT.
ALL RIGHT.
I'LL TAKE CARE OF HIM.
POLICE!
HEY, WAIT A MINUTE!
DO YOU GUYS HAVE A WARRANT?
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
WE WANT YOUR BOYFRIEND,
THAT'S WHAT.
WINDOW! WINDOW!
YOU KNOW, YOU CAN'T
KEEP BUSTING--
SHUT UP!
WAIT! WAIT FOR ME!
Franklin:
COME ON, JAMES!
[GUNSHOTS]
AAH!
UNH!
WHAT THE HELL
ARE YOU SHOOTING AT?
HE'S A COP KILLER,
OFFICER PICKETT!
DON'T BE TRYING TO KILL
EVERYBODY, WILL YOU?
AW, FOR
CHRIST'S SAKE!
RIGHT HERE. THIS IS IT.
TURN HERE.
ALL YOU'VE BEEN DOING
IS BITCHIN' AND BITCHIN'
EVER SINCE WE GOT TOGETHER.
SO I'M BITCHING. I'M NOT
USED TO GETTING SHOT AT.
WELL, I'M NOT
USED TO PEOPLE
GETTING ME INTO SHIT,
SO SHUT THE HELL UP.
NOW, THAT FRENCH DUDE
WHO KILLED THOSE COPS
HAD A STAMP ON HIS HAND
FROM THIS CLUB.
I HEARD A LOT OF EUROTRASH
HANG OUT DOWN HERE.
NOW, WE'RE
GONNA GO IN HERE.
IF WE SEE HIM, WE'RE
GONNA CALL THE COPS,
GET THEM DOWN HERE,
GET HIM BUSTED,
AND CLEAR MY GODDAMN
NAME TONIGHT.
CAN I--CAN I HANDLE THIS?
[KNOCKING]
GOOD EVENING. JAMES RUSSELL,
CHANNEL 12 NEWS.
WE'RE DOING A REPORT
ON LOCAL NIGHTCLUBS.
I'D LIKE TO ASK YOU
A FEW QUESTIONS.
OH, YOU'RE
THE INVESTIGATIVE REPORTER.
YES, I AM.
GET THE FUCK
OUT OF HERE.
HA HA!
WHOO, DAMN.
YOU GOT A LOT OF PULL
IN THIS TOWN.
I COULD DO A REPORT
ON THIS SHITHOLE
THAT'D
CLOSE IT DOWN FOREVER.
[CHUCKLES]
FUCK THAT, MAN.
IF WE CAN'T GO
TO THE RED CAMEL,
RED CAMEL COMES TO US.
WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
JUST COME ON.
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
COME ON.
SHUT THE HELL UP.
BRING YOUR ASS ON.
GIMME A QUARTER.
HEY, HURRY UP AND
GIMME A QUARTER!
WHO ARE YOU CALLING?
HELLO?
IT'S MIKE VERMISHKI.
REMEMBER ME?
YOU DONE FUCKED WITH ME
FOR THE LAST TIME, GODDAMN IT!
THERE'S A BOMB
IN THE BUILDING!
THAT'S RIGHT! A GODDAMN BOMB
GET YOUR ASS OUT...
FUCK YOU! FUCK YOU!
THERE'S A GODDAMN BOMB
IN THE BUILDING,
AND IT'S FIXIN' TO BLOW!
YOU BETTER GET YOUR ASS
OUT RIGHT NOW!
YOU HAVE CROSSED
THE FUCKING--
WATCH THIS.
5...4...3...
2...1.
COME ON!
COME ON, MOVE IT!
[SCREAMING]
VOILà.
Bouncer:
MOVE IT! MOVE! MOVE!
RUN ALREADY! RUN!
THAT'S HIM RIGHT THERE.
THAT'S ONE OF THEM
RIGHT THERE!
YOU SURE?
I'M SURE!
DAMN, THAT BITCH FINE.
WAIT A MINUTE.
OK, NOW LET'S GO.
COME ON.
FRANKLIN.
THIS IS CRAZY.
OH!
OHH!
[TIRES SQUEAL]
[WHIRRING]
COME ON.
[FOOTSTEPS]
HEY, WHAT THE HELL IS--
[HIP-HOP MUSIC PLAYING]
[MUSIC STOPS]
WHEN WE GET IN HERE,
YOU DON'T SAY NOTHIN'.
ONLY 2 WHITE PEOPLE
DONE WALKED IN HERE.
YOU KEEP YOUR MOUTH SHUT, YOU'LL
BE THE FIRST ONE TO WALK OUT.
OH, AND ANOTHER THING.
YOU AIN'T WHITE, YOU MIXED.
YOUR MAMA BLACK AND YOUR DADDY
PUERTO RICAN IF THEY ASK YOU.
WHAT?
YO, MAN. AARON HERE?
TELL HIM FRANKLIN OUT HERE
AND WANT TO TALK TO HIM.
NAW. AARON DON'T KNOW
NO DAMN FRANKLIN.
HOW THE HELL YOU KNOW, MAN?
TELL HIM I WAS THERE WHEN HE
SHOT BABY BRO AT MACARTHUR PARK.
WHERE'D HE
SHOOT BABY BRO?
AT MACARTHUR PARK,
YOU BIG DUMB--
NAW! WHERE'D
HE SHOOT HIM?
IN THE ASS! EVERYBODY KNOW
HE GOT SHOT IN THE ASS!
DON'T EVER PLAY ME
LIKE THAT, PLAYER-HATER.
I'M SORRY.
I WAS JUST PLAYIN'.
Bouncer:
BLACK BASTARD.
AARON! WHAT'S HAPPENING?
WHAT'S POPPING?
WHAT'S UP, FRANKLIN?
HEY, MAN,
I TRIED CALLING YOU,
BUT THE PHONE--
COULDN'T GET THROUGH.
BUT ANYWAY,
I NEED YOUR HELP, MAN.
I NEED SOME GATS ON CREDIT.
AGAIN?
AGAIN? OH, LAST TIME, YOU KNOW
THAT WASN'T MY MISTAKE.
THAT WAS LITTLE JOHNNY
WHO FUCKED UP THE MONEY.
YEAH. YOU KNOW
LITTLE JOHNNY
IS INVISIBLE JOHNNY
NOW, RIGHT?
YEAH, I KNOW.
I WENT TO THE FUNERAL.
THAT WAS FUCKED UP
WHAT YOU DID.
IT WAS CLOSED CASKET
AND EVERYTHING.
BUT ANYWAY, I APPRECIATE THIS
IF YOU DO THIS, MAN.
YOU GET ME 2 COURTSIDE,
IF IT GOES 7 GAMES,
ON THE FLOOR,
AND I DON'T MEAN THAT
SHIT BEHIND THE BACKBOARD.
THAT WAS A MISTAKE. I GAVE YOU
THE WRONG TICKETS BY MISTAKE.
COOL. IT'S DONE. IF IT GOES
700 GAMES, I GOT YOU.
DONE.
WHAT THE FUCK IS
THIS SHIT OVER HERE?
OH, HE'S COOL. HE'S JUST
A REPORTER FROM CHANNEL 5 NEWS.
REPORTER?
AARON! AARON! AA-RON!
MAN, WHAT THE HELL--
WHAT'S HE REPORTING ON,
MY LIFESTYLE?
HE GONNA HELP ME OUT!
HELP--HELP YOU OUT?
HELP YOU DO WHAT?
HELP ME TO CLEAR MY NAME!
LOOK, FRANKLIN,
YOU FUCK ME UP HERE,
THE ONLY THING YOUR NAME
IS GONNA BE GOOD FOR
IS A GODDAMN TOMBSTONE,
YOU HEAR ME?
HE DON'T KNOW NOTHIN'
ABOUT YOU. HE HERE FOR ME.
HE DON'T KNOW NOTHIN' ABOUT THE
HOS AND THE GUNS AND THE DRUGS.
AARON! AARON!
YOU KNOW I WON'T BRING NO SHIT
DOWN ON YOU LIKE THAT.
LOOK AT ME NOW.
HOW FAR WE GO BACK?
ELEMENTARY...
JUMP ROPE?
HIDE-AND-GO-SEEK?
PITTY-PAT?
RED LIGHT-GREEN LIGHT?
RED LIGHT-GREEN LIGHT.
NOW, WHAT WOULD OUR MAMAS
SAY TO SEE US LIKE THIS?
ALL THE STUFF
WE BEEN THROUGH?
WE BOYS, MAN.
YEAH.
COOL?
[CLICK]
Aaron:
COME WITH ME.
SO YOU SAY
YOU GOT PROBLEMS, HUH?
DAMN.
ITTY-BITTY,
TEENY-WEENY PROBLEMS.
BIG FAT-ASS PROBLEMS.
I GOT WHAT YOU NEED.
NOW, THERE'S NO ITCH
THAT AN...
HK-MP5 CAN'T SCRATCH.
UNLESS, OF COURSE,
YOU WANT A...
UZI...
WITH A WILSON
SUPPRESSER ON IT.
VERY NICE.
VERY...
URBAN.
I'D GO WITH
THE HECKLER & KOCH.
WELL, IT'S GOT
A CLOSED BOLT,
AS OPPOSED
TO THE UZI.
IT'S GOT A FASTER
CYCLIC RATE,
BETTER SIGHTS,
REAR APERTURE.
IT'S GERMAN,
AS OPPOSED
TO ISRAELI.
IT'S MUCH MORE
ACCURATE THAN--
LOOK HERE,
DAN RATHER.
YOU SURE YOU NOT
A FUCKING COP?
YEAH, I'M SURE I'M
NOT A GODDAMNED COP.
I DID A REPORT
LAST YEAR
ON STREET WEAPONS,
ALL RIGHT?
WELL, IF YOU DON'T
SHUT UP,
THE LAST REPORT
YOU'RE GONNA HEAR
IS THIS UZI GOING OFF
IN YOUR ASS, ALL RIGHT?
AARON, I DON'T MEAN
TO DISRESPECT YOUR SHIT
OR NOTHING LIKE THAT,
BUT THIS SHIT HERE
IS TOO MUCH. TOO HEAVY.
I NEED SOMETHING LIGHTER
'CAUSE WE'RE GONNA BE
DOING A LOT OF RUNNING.
SEE THIS HERE?
ONE OR 2 OF THESE.
THIS IS ALL I NEED
RIGHT HERE.
COUPLE OF THESE,
AND I'M COOL, MAN.
AND I'M GONNA PAY YOU BACK.
YOU KNOW I'M GOOD FOR IT.
UH, FRANKLIN.
HUH? WHAT?
CALL ME IF YOU GET
IN TROUBLE, ALL RIGHT?
I'M GONNA CALL YOU, MAN.
AND THANK YOU AGAIN.
I'M GONNA GET YOU THAT
MONEY SOON. I PROMISE.
HEY, I JUST GOT
THE INTERPOL REPORT BACK
ON THE JOHN DOE
THEY PICKED UP
AT THE AIRPORT
YESTERDAY.
THIS IS OUR GUY.
RAYMOND VILLARD.
LAST KNOWN RESIDENCE:
BELGIUM.
HE'S WANTED FOR KILLING
A COP IN PARIS,
CONVICTED OF A JEWELRY
HEIST IN LONDON,
WANTED FOR KILLING
SOMEONE ELSE IN COLOGNE.
IT GOES ON AND ON.
I DON'T THINK SO, MAN.
THIS GUY COULD TURN UP
LYING FLAT ON HIS FACE
IN THAT BUS.
FORENSICS AIN'T DONE WITH
THE BODIES YET, YOU KNOW?
I STILL THINK
HATCHETT'S OUR MAN.
NO, NOT ACCORDING
TO THIS.
GOT A NICE VIDEOTAPE
OF YOUR SUSPECT HERE.
IT'S FROM THE SECURITY
CAMERA IN THE DELI.
WE'LL SEE.
[HUMMING WEDDING MARCH]
TV: AND NOW A LIVE
REPORT FROM THE SCENE.
Newscaster:
A COLD-BLOODED MURDER
LAST NIGHT IN A DELI
HERE IN DOWNTOWN L.A.
HOMICIDE DETECTIVES HAVE ALREADY
IDENTIFIED THE 2 GUNMEN
THROUGH THE USE OF
A SURVEILLANCE CAMERA TAPE.
WE'RE TOLD THEY ARE
FRANKLIN MAURICE HATCHETT
AND AN UNNAMED REPORTER
FROM CHANNEL 12 NEWS.
HATCHETT IS ALREADY WANTED
IN CONNECTION WITH THE DEATH
OF 14 INMATES AND 2 POLICEMEN
DURING A DARING
PRISON ESCAPE AT--
I HAVE THIS LATE WORD
JUST IN.
POLICE HAVE NOW
RELEASED THE NAME
OF THE SECOND SUSPECT,
AND HE IS JAMES RUSSELL
OF CHANNEL 12 NEWS.
WE'LL, OF COURSE,
CONTINUE TO UPDATE YOU
ON THIS BREAKING STORY
AS DEVELOPMENTS WARRANT.
NOW BACK TO YOU
IN THE STUDIO.
[GULP]
¶ TEENSY ¶
¶ WEENSY SPIDER ¶
¶ WALKED UP
THE WATERSPOUT ¶
[GIGGLES]
¶ DOWN CAME THE RAIN ¶
¶ AND WASHED-- ¶
WHOA HO HO! HEY, BOYS.
HOW YOU DOING?
GOOD MORNING, FOLKS.
COME ON, SIT DOWN.
HAVE SOMETHING TO EAT.
NO, WE DON'T HAVE TIME.
I GOTTA TALK TO GRACE.
I'LL TAKE
A LITTLE SOMETHING,
IF YOU DON'T MIND?
'CAUSE I'M A LITTLE HUNGRY.
I WAS WONDERING
WHEN YOU WAS GONNA
ASK ME TO SIT DOWN.
I THINK WE'RE INTERRUPTING
A VERY TENDER BREAKFAST HERE.
WHAT DO YOU SAY THAT WE--
NO, THAT'S COOL.
IS IT COOL, GUY?
IT'S COOL. THE KIDS SAY
IT'S COOL, RIGHT? COOL.
GO IN THERE AND TAKE CARE
OF YOUR BUSINESS WITH GRACE.
TALK TO GRACE AS LONG
AS YOU WANT.
I'M GONNA BE HERE EATING.
I'M GONNA COME AND GET YOU
WHEN I'M THROUGH. GO ON.
I LOVE THAT MAN.
HE'S NERVOUS
ABOUT THE WEDDING.
BEST FRIEND
IN THE WORLD.
DID YOU TELL VIC
I WANT HIM TO CALL ME?
YEAH, I TOLD HIM. HE SAID
HE WAS GONNA CALL YOU SOON.
HE WAS HAPPY
TO HEAR FROM YOU, TOO.
TERRIFIC. WHAT DO YOU WANT
FOR BREAKFAST?
WHATEVER Y'ALL GOT.
I CAN EAT ANYTHING.
YOU WANT SOME BACON
AND EGGS?
OH, WAIT A MINUTE.
YOU'RE ITALIAN.
LISTEN, MAKE HIM
A NICE VILOSH.
PUT A NICE RAGU
AND SOME SAUSAGES
ON THE SIDE, ALL RIGHT?
IS THAT OK WITH YOU?
Franklin: OK WITH ME.
YEAH, AND GIVE ME SOME
ITALIAN GRITS ON THE SIDE,
IF YOU DON'T MIND.
THANKS, MA.
THAT'S YOUR MAMA?
YEAH.
GUY!
THAT'S HOW THE RICH
STAY RICH.
KEEP IT IN THE FAMILY.
SO HOW'S THE MISTRESS
OF THE HOUSE THIS MORNING?
I'VE NEVER BEEN
ANYBODY'S MISTRESS.
HE WAS MY FIRST,
MY LAST,
MY EVERYTHING.
Guy: BABY.
EXCUSE ME.
YOU PISSED HER OFF.
SHE ALWAYS LIKE THAT?
YEAH.
MAN!
BUT SHE'S WORTH IT.
WELL...
WHAT'S GOING ON?
OH, SHIT!
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
WHAT'S IN THE PAPER?
UH, NOTHING.
SO WHAT'D YOU GET
THE NEWLYWEDS
FOR THEIR WEDDING GIFT?
OH HO HO.
COME ON. I'LL SHOW YOU.
YOU GOT IT ALREADY?
YEAH. COME ON.
[DEAN MARTIN SONG PLAYING
IN BACKGROUND]
GAWD...
DAMN!
GUY, THIS IS
ANOTHER HOUSE, MAN.
[CHUCKLES]
WHEW. SHIT.
HOW RICH ARE YOU,
MAN?
[CHUCKLES]
LOAN ME
A MILLION DOLLARS.
[LAUGHTER]
YOU GONNA LOAN IT
TO ME?
I WAS JUST PLAYING.
HOW MANY PEOPLE
SLEEP IN THIS BED?
ME AND CONNIE.
THAT'S IT.
THAT'S IT?
THIS IS INCREDIBLE.
LET ME SPEND THE NIGHT.
ANYTIME. YOU READY?
I'M READY?
IS THIS THE GIFT?
THIS IS IT.
GET READY.
WHEW.
WHEW-HOO.
HEH HEH.
THAT'S--THAT'S NICE.
THAT'S TIGHT, MAN.
THAT'S NICE, BUT, UH...
WHAT?
HMM?
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
NOTHING, NOTHING.
THAT'S COOL.
THAT'S ALL RIGHT.
YOU HOOKING THEM UP ON
SOME LIBERACE-TYPE SHIT.
WHAT'S WRONG WITH IT?
THAT'S BULGARI.
FORGET ABOUT IT, MAN.
IT'S COOL. IT'S COOL.
BELIEVE ME, IT'S COOL.
I--BELIEVE ME.
THEY'RE NOT GONNA
LIKE IT?
OH, HEY,
YOU KNOW SOMETHING.
DID THEY SAY SOMETHING
TO YOU?
AW, FORGET ABOUT IT, MAN.
I CAN'T BE SAYING NOTHING.
I'M NOT IN THE FAMILY
LIKE THAT.
COME ON. BE A FRIEND.
TELL ME.
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT,
ALL RIGHT.
NOW, IF I TELL YOU THIS,
YOU CAN'T THEM I TOLD YOU.
WHY WOULD I DO THAT?
OK.
I HAPPEN TO KNOW
THAT THE NEWLYWEDS
WANT A DOPE RIDE.
OH, NO. WE DON'T DO DOPE
IN THIS FAMILY.
NO, NO.
NO, NO, NO, NO.
NOT DOPE. A RIDE.
WHERE DO THEY WANNA GO?
MY CHAUFFEUR
WILL TAKE THEM ANYWHERE.
NOT A RIDE.
I MEAN A CAR, VEHICLE.
OH, A CAR.
SURE, I GOT A LOT OF CARS.
WHICH ONE DID THEY WANT?
THEY WANT THE BENTLEY?
THE ROLLS?
NO, NO, NO, NO.
NOT ANY TYPE OF CAR.
THEY WANT A EUROPEAN-TYPE
EX-RACER CAR.
WHERE AM I GONNA GET
SOMETHING LIKE THAT
BY TOMORROW MORNING?
I THINK
WE CAN GET ONE.
YOU DO?
I KNOW A PLACE.
ALL RIGHT.
I'LL TAKE THESE BACK.
WHY DON'T YOU LET ME
KEEP THEM?
I MEAN, I'LL GIVE THEM
BACK TO YOU.
I'M JUST PLAYING...
UNLESS YOU'RE GONNA
LET ME KEEP 'EM.
YOU BROUGHT A KILLER
INTO MY PARENTS' HOUSE!
ARE YOU EVEN LISTENING
TO ME?
FRANKLIN MAY BE
A LOT OF THINGS,
BUT HE IS NOT A KILLER.
YOU GOTTA TRUST ME
ON THIS ONE.
I AM TRYING.
WE'RE SUPPOSED TO BE
IN THIS TOGETHER.
WE ARE.
WHAT ABOUT TOMORROW?
I'LL BE HERE.
YOU ARE WANTED
FOR MURDER.
WE CAN'T GET MARRIED WHEN
YOU'RE WANTED FOR MURDER.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
Franklin:
OH, MAN, NEVER?
Guy: YEAH.
I'M TELLING YOU, MAN,
WE'RE GONNA HAVE FUN
DOWN AT THE AUTO EXPO.
OH, FUCK ME.
[TIRES SQUEAL]
NEXT ITEM UP
IS A MERCEDES
1957 GULL-WING.
ONLY 1,400
OF THESE WERE MADE.
LET'S OPEN UP THE BIDDING
AT $100,000.
100'S THERE. 105 NOW.
105. GO 110.
110 OUT BACK.
115 TO THE LADY THERE.
AND 120...
ALL MY OLD FRIENDS
IN HERE.
WHERE'S TRUMP?
Auctioneer: $190,000.
HEY, MAN.
HOW YOU DOING?
HOW THOSE 7-11
CHAINS GOING?
OH, YES.
GREAT.
LET ME REMIND YOU
THAT CARY GRANT DROVE
THIS CAR IN MONACO
WHILE FILMING
TO CATCH A THIEF.
CARY GRANT
DROVE THAT CAR.
IS THAT THE MOST
BEAUTIFUL CAR
YOU EVER SAW
IN YOUR LIFE?
NAW, THAT'S NOT IT.
I'LL TELL YOU
WHEN I SEE IT.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
IT'S BEAUTIFUL.
TRUST ME.
THAT'S NOT IT.
Auctioneer:
300,000 THERE NOW.
310. STILL BIDDING.
310. GO 20.
320,000 TO YOU THERE.
320,000. AND 30.
STILL BIDDING
STRONG THERE.
AND 340,000
AGAINST YOU STILL.
350,000 IS NOW THE BID.
ANY ADVANCE? LAST CALL.
ALL THROUGH.
ALL DONE AT $350,000.
SOLD TO THE GENTLEMEN
IN THE BURNOOSE
WITH THE 3 LOVELY LADIES.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
NOW THAT CAR GOES
TO ARABIA.
NAW, I HEARD HE DIDN'T
REALLY DRIVE THAT CAR.
THAT'S IKE TURNER'S
OLD CAR.
I SEEN THAT CAR.
WHO'S IKE TURNER?
OLD PIMP.
DO I HAVE 120?
120,000 BID THERE.
THANK YOU.
130. STILL BIDDING HERE.
130 THOU--OH, AND 40,000
STILL BIDDING HERE.
140,000 IS THE BID.
AND 150, STILL.
THAT'S THE ONE.
NAW, THAT'S NOT IT.
NO.
DO I HEAR 500,000?
AND 500,000 I DO.
AND 550?
550,000 THERE.
AND 600,000 HERE.
THANK YOU.
AND 650,000 THERE.
THAT'S NOT IT.
THAT'S BEAUTIFUL.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
THAT'S NOT IT.
THE NEXT ITEM
UP ON THE BLOCK
IS A 1951 JAGUAR
XK-140 ROADSTER
CUSTOM BUILT FOR
PRINCESS GRACE OF MONACO.
MINT CONDITION.
BIDDING WILL COMMENCE
AT $100,000.
100,000.
THIS IS THE ONE.
THIS IS THE RIDE.
YOU SURE?
I'M POSITIVE.
THANK GOD.
105.
105. THANK YOU.
105, 105.
LOVELY 105.
WHO'LL GIVE ME 110?
110 THERE NOW.
110, NOW 115.
115?
115. YES, 115 IS BID.
DO I HEAR 120?
120 IS NOW THE BID.
THANK YOU.
125?
125 HERE. THANK YOU.
HERE WE GO. AND 130?
130 TO YOU, SIR?
130.
130 HE DOES.
130 IS NOW THE BID.
130. DO I HEAR 135?
135 TO THE GENTLEMAN
TAKING AIM
AT THIS MECHANICAL
MASTERPIECE.
DO I HEAR 140?
140 TO THE GENTLEMAN WHO'S
WELCOMING ALL CHALLENGERS.
140. THANK YOU.
DO I HEAR 145?
145 BID TO MY RIGHT NOW.
[WHISPERS]
Suck my dick.
I BELIEVE THAT'S 150.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
STOP IT, STOP IT.
DO I HEAR 155?
155. STILL BIDDING
STRONG NOW.
OH?
DO I HEAR 160?
160 IS BID IN TIME
TO MY LEFT NOW.
WHO IS THIS GUY?
I DON'T KNOW. I GOTTA
USE THE BATHROOM.
I'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
WE'RE IN THE MIDDLE
OF--
[SPEAKING FRENCH]
Auctioneer:
WHO'LL GO 165,000?
HELLO, POLICE?
LOOK, Y'ALL NEED TO COME OUT
TO THE AUTO AUCTION RIGHT NOW
THE COP KILLER'S
DOWN HERE.
YEAH. THEY DOWN HERE, MAN.
THEY SHOOTING AND SHIT.
SLAPPING PEOPLE.
THEY ACTING A FOOL, MAN!
HEY, COPS WANNA TALK TO YOU.
THEY ON THEIR WAY.
COPS WANNA TALK TO YOU.
THEY WANNA KNOW
WHERE TO PICK YOU UP AT.
YOU'RE DEAD.
THEY COPS ARE ON THEIR WAY,
MAN! HOLD UP!
ONE OF THEM DRESSED
IN BLACK,
AND THE OTHER ONE DRESSED
IN A FUCKED-UP TUXEDO.
COME ON DOWN! HURRY UP, MAN!
PEOPLE DYING HERE! HURRY UP!
Auctioneer: 175. STILL
BIDDING STRONG TO MY RIGHT.
DO I HEAR 180?
180!
180 IS NOW THE BID THERE.
180 NOW.
185,000...
WHAT THE FUCK
IS GOING ON HERE?
MAN, WHAT THE HELL
YOU DOING DOWN HERE?
YOU AND I ARE GONNA
SETTLE THIS
RIGHT HERE, RIGHT NOW.
YOU KNOW, THANKS TO YOU,
I'M WANTED FOR MURDER
NOW, TOO.
I WANT SOME ANSWERS.
HEY, MAN, ME AND GUY
JUST DOWN HERE
CHECKING OUT
SOME FLY RIDES
AND MACKING SOME HOS
AND CHILLIN'.
IMAGINE THAT.
JUST LIKE A "G" DAWG
ON A FLY TIP
FLOSSIN' WITH THE POSSE.
CUTTIN' IN THE CRIB.
WHAT THE FUCK
DOES THAT MEAN?!
MAN, I DON'T WANNA HAVE
TO BEAT YOUR ASS,
BUT I WILL BEAT YOUR ASS!
OK.
NOW, STAY THE FUCK
OUT OF MY FACE, MAN!
I'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
HMM. YOU FUCKED UP.
YOU LIKE THAT, HUH?
YOU DONE FUCKED UP NOW,
MAN! COME ON. RIGHT HERE.
YEAH.
OH, YEAH.
COME ON, COME ON.
WANT SOME MORE?
FUCKER.
FUCKING WITH ME?
WHY THE FUCK YOU DO THAT?
OH!
GOD! AAH.
[GROANING]
Auctioneer: 240.
DO I HEAR 240,000?
240,000 BID THERE.
THANK YOU.
STILL BIDDING.
240,000 HERE.
250,000 IF YOU WISH,
SIR.
250,000?
HOW YOU DOING?
THIS STRUNZ
WON'T GIVE UP.
LET'S GET OUT.
AT 250,000, IF YOU WISH.
FUCK HIM.
YEAH?
YEAH.
ANY ADVANCE? SIR?
Auctioneer: SIR?
$250,000!
HA!
[APPLAUSE]
$250,000 IS BID HERE
TO MY LEFT NOW.
250,000 IS NOW THE BID.
I BELIEVE WE'VE LOST
OUR COMPETITOR.
250 GOING ONCE.
GOING TWICE.
SOLD TO
THE GENTLEMAN THERE.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
YOU THE MAN!
I'LL MEET YOU OUT FRONT,
ALL RIGHT?
WHAT?
MEET YOU OUT FRONT.
[POWER TOOLS WHIRRING]
COME ON, BABY.
WHERE YOU AT?
SHIT. MMM.
NO, I DON'T THINK
IT'LL GO OVER.
I'LL PLACE A BID.
VERY GOOD. NOW,
WHAT ABOUT NUMBER--
[STARTS ENGINE]
[HORNS HONKING]
AAH!
[HORN HONKS]
Franklin: WHOA!
Franklin: AAH!
[HORNS HONKING]
[CRASH]
COME ON!
OHH!
[CACKLING]
OH.
OH!
FRENCHY! HA HA!
[HORNS HONKING]
[YELLING IN FRENCH]
WAIT A MINUTE.
SO THIS JAMES
IS A MURDERER,
IS THAT IT?
NO, DADDY.
JAMES IS INNOCENT.
AND THIS OTHER GUY,
IS HE VIC DAMONE'S SON
OR ISN'T HE?
I DON'T KNOW.
SO WHAT ARE YOU TELLING ME,
HE'S 100% MOOLIE?
WHO CARES?
I HAD MOM MAKE HIM
A MOZZARELLA OMELET.
THAT LYING SON OF A BITCH
BASTARD.
HEY, THERE'S NO WEDDING.
YOU'RE NOT GONNA MARRY
THIS JAMES. NO WAY.
BUT WE'VE GOT 300 PEOPLE
COMING HERE TOMORROW.
GOOD. THEY COME HERE,
THEY EAT, THEY DRINK,
THEY SING,
THEY GO THE FUCK HOME!
AND WHAT AM I SUPPOSED
TO TELL THEM?
YOU TELL THEM THAT OUR GRACE
WAS ABOUT TO BE MARRIED
TO SOME NO-GOOD,
LIMP-DICK BASTARD!
HE IS NOT LIMP-DICKED,
DADDY.
I DON'T WANNA
HEAR THAT!
OH, DADDY, PLEASE.
I LOVE HIM,
AND I TRUST HIM.
LET'S NOT JUMP
TO CONCLUSIONS.
I'M GONNA
TELL YOU SOMETHING.
THIS JAMES COMES IN HERE,
I BREAK HIS LEGS FOR HIM.
AND AS FAR
AS VIC DAMONE JR.--
THAT'S NOT
VIC DAMONE JR.!
WHAT THE HELL
AM I SAYING?
HONEY, HAVE A DRINK.
ME, TOO.
AHH.
[SHOUTING IN ITALIAN]
OH, SHIT.
OH, SHIT!
GODDAMN.
OHH.
[STEVIE WONDER MUSIC
PLAYING IN BACKGROUND]
YOU SURE NOBODY
FOLLOWED YOU?
YEAH.
YOU SURE?
MM-HMM.
ARE YOU SURE?
YES, NIGGER,
I'M SURE, OK?
LOOK UNDER THE TABLE.
WHAT?
LOOK AT THAT.
NO, SEE YOU DONE GONE
AND DONE IT NOW, OK?
'CAUSE THIS SCARES ME.
WHAT YOU TALKING ABOUT?
THIS GONNA TAKE CARE OF US
FOR THE REST OF OUR LIFE.
WE WON'T HAVE TO DO
SHIT ELSE.
WHAT WE GONNA DO?
WHERE WE GONNA GO?
WE CAN GO WHEREVER
THE HELL WE WANNA GO
WITH THIS SHIT, GIRL.
I WAS THINKING ABOUT
BUYING A SMALL COUNTRY.
BABY, THIS IS WRONG, OK?
THIS IS WRONG.
THIS IS RIGHT!
IT CAN'T GET NO RIGHTER!
THIS IS THE ONLY WAY
OUT OF THIS SHIT I'M IN.
HERE'S THE NUMBER
FOR THIS POLICEMAN.
YOU WANT ME
TO CALL THE COPS?!
SHH!
MOTHERFUCKERS ARE TRYING
TO KILL ME,
YOU WANT ME TO CALL THEM
SO THEY CAN SHOOT ME.
MY BABY AIN'T GONNA BE
NO FUGITIVE.
YOU DON'T WANNA CALL
THE COPS, THAT IS FINE.
MAYBE THAT REPORTER GUY CAN
CLEAR THIS WHOLE THING UP.
WHO, JAMES RUSSELL?
YES.
SHIT.
FUCKER
JAMES RUSSELL.
FUCK HIM.
AND DON'T GIVE ME
THAT LOOK
'CAUSE IT AIN'T
GONNA WORK.
DON'T EVEN GIVE ME
THAT LOOK.
I SEE YOU
LOOKING AT ME.
MONSIEUR RUSSELL...
ONE MORE TIME.
THINK.
WHERE ARE MY DIAMONDS?
[PAGER BEEPING]
[BEEPING STOPS]
GIMME A KISS.
NO.
[LOUD SMOOCH NOISES]
[CELL PHONE RINGS]
YO, JAMES, THAT YOU?
I WANT
THE DIAMONDS
OR YOUR
PARTNER'S DEAD.
PARTNER? I AIN'T GOT
NO GODDAMNED PARTNER!
WHO THE FUCK IS THIS?
FRANKLIN, LISTEN TO ME.
I'M WITH SOME PEOPLE RIGHT NOW
WHO'VE PROMISED TO KILL ME
UNLESS YOU GIVE THEM
THOSE DIAMONDS.
YOU KNOW, THE ONES
YOU FORGOT TO MENTION!
WHAT DIAMONDS?
THE FUCKING DIAMONDS,
YOU PRICK!
MEDULLA OBLONGATA.
WHAT?
TELL THEM TO SHOOT YOU
IN MEDULLA OBLONGATA
RIGHT BEHIND THE EAR.
YOU WON'T FEEL SHIT.
THIS ISN'T A FUCKING JOKE,
FRANKLIN.
I'M IN SOME DEEP SHIT HERE.
LISTEN TO ME.
3 A.M.
HANGAR NUMBER 7.
LONG BEACH AIRPORT.
KEEP THE DIAMONDS
IN A PLASTIC BAG.
THEY WILL BE
WEIGHED.
KISS MY ASS!
WE MEET WHERE I SAY
WE MEET,
FRENCH MOTHERFUCKER.
WHAT HAPPENED?
HE HUNG UP.
WE MEET ON HIS TURF,
THEN YOUR ASS BE ALL ALONE.
MEET ON MY TURF,
AT LEAST WE GOT A CHANCE.
HE'LL CALL BACK.
[RING]
WHAT'D I TELL YOU?
ALL RIGHT, MOTHERFUCKER,
THIS IS THE DEAL.
Woman: WATCH YOUR LANGUAGE!
MAMA, MAMA! MAMA,
I AIN'T KNOW IT YOU!
NO, I AIN'T KILLED
NO COPS.
MAMA, CALL ME BACK, OK?
CALL ME BACK. MAMA,
STOP WATCHING THE NEWS.
DON'T BE BELIEVING
EVERYTHING ON THE NEWS.
[RING]
WHO IS THIS?
I'M LISTENING.
ALL RIGHT, GODDAMN IT,
THIS IS THE DEAL.
50 YARD LINE, COLISEUM,
3 A.M.
AND IF JIMMY BOY
AIN'T ALIVE,
YOU CAN KISS
THEM DIAMONDS GOOD-BYE.
HEY, CARMINE,
TONIGHT I'M GONNA
PAY YOUR ASS OFF...
IN DIAMONDS.
DIAMONDS, HUH?
WHERE'S A PIECE OF SHIT
LIKE YOU GET DIAMONDS?
Franklin:
COLISEUM. 3 A.M.
[HANGS UP]
[RING]
WILLIAMS.
Franklin: HEY, COP.
YEAH?
THIS IS
FRANKLIN HATCHETT.
MEET ME AT THE COLISEUM,
3 A.M.
YEAH. 3 A.M. COLISEUM.
BE THERE.
YEAH, WE'LL BE THERE.
RIGHT.
THAT WAS HATCHETT.
HE WANTS
TO TURN HIMSELF IN.
I'M GONNA GO TELL
THE CAPTAIN.
NO. OH, OH, OH, OH.
NO WAY, BUDDY.
THIS IS OUR COLLAR.
YOU AND ME. US.
LET'S GO.
[SNORING]
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
[RING]
HELLO.
Franklin: ROLAND, IT'S ME.
WAKE YOUR OLD ASS UP.
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
HEY, I NEED YOU DOWN
AT THE BOOTH TONIGHT.
I'M GONNA OWE YOU
FOR THIS ONE, ALL RIGHT?
¶ IF YOU WANT ME TO STAY ¶
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
¶ I'LL BE AROUND TODAY ¶
[RING]
¶ TO BE AVAILABLE
FOR YOU TO SEE ¶
[ANSWERING MACHINE
PICKS UP]
Franklin: YO, AARON!
AARON, YOU THERE, MAN?
PICK UP THE PHONE, MAN!
HEY, YOU SAID CALL YOU
IF I NEED YOU.
I NEED YOU
AT THE COLISEUM TONIGHT.
DON'T LET A BROTHER DOWN.
AARON!
[HELICOPTER BLADES
WHIRRING]
DROP THE GUN!
WHOA. WHAT THE FUCK
Y'ALL DOING?
IT'S JUST
FOR PROTECTION, MAN.
DON'T YOU EVEN SCRATCH YOUR
SKINNY, SPANKY ASS, PAL,
OR YOU'RE FUCKING DEAD.
HEY, WAIT A MINUTE!
I'M THE MOTHERFUCKER
WHO CALLED Y'ALL.
REMEMBER?
THE DUDE YOU'RE LOOKING
FOR IS ON HIS WAY.
Y'ALL JUST CALM
THE FUCK DOWN.
Y'ALL GONNA GET MEDALS
FOR THIS SHIT.
I'M HELPING Y'ALL OUT. Y'ALL
TRYING TO KILL A NIGGER.
HAND OVER THE GUN!
I AIN'T
HANDING OVER SHIT.
HAND OVER THAT GUN
RIGHT NOW.
HOW DO I KNOW Y'ALL
AIN'T GONNA SHOOT ME?
I'M GONNA SHOOT YOU
IF YOU DON'T!
I'M GONNA SHOOT, THEN!
WE'LL BE DEAD MOTHERFUCKERS!
HAND OVER THE GUN!
SHOOT, THEN, SHOOT!
HEY!
HEY, WILLIAMS,
SHUT THE FUCK UP!
FUCK YOU, THEN! I AIN'T
PUTTING NOTHING DOWN.
NOW, LOOK,
NOBODY'S GONNA SHOOT YOU
IF YOU HAND ME THE GUN.
YOU GOTTA TRUST SOMEBODY.
I DON'T TRUST NOBODY.
LOWER THE GUN.
YOU LOWER YOUR GUN.
HAND IT OVER TO ME.
NOBODY WANTS TO DIE.
COME ON, NOW, MAN.
NICE AND EASY.
JUST HAND ME THE GUN.
IF I GIVE YOU THE GUN,
AND HE SHOOTS ME,
I'M GONNA KICK YOUR ASS.
HE WILL NOT SHOOT YOU
IF YOU GIVE ME THE GUN.
CONTROL
THAT WHITE BOY.
ALL RIGHT.
BACKUP'S ON THE WAY,
AND YOU'RE GONNA TELL ME
WHERE THE DIAMONDS ARE.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT,
"BACKUP'S ON THE WAY"?
AND WHOEVER SAID SOMETHING
ABOUT SOME DIAMONDS?
LIEUTENANT, WHAT THE HELL'S
GOING ON AROUND HERE?
GODDAMN!
YOU SON OF A BITCH.
YOU JUST
KILLED MY PARTNER.
YOU JUST KILLED
YOUR GODDAMN PARTNER!
NO, NO. THIS IS YOUR GUN.
WHERE ARE THE DIAMONDS?
DETECTIVE PICKETT.
YOU HAVE MY DIAMONDS.
AAH!
Carmine:
YOU THREE GO THAT WAY.
YOU TWO GO WITH GUIDO.
FIND FRANKLIN
AND HOLD HIM FOR ME.
HEY, ROLAND!
ROLAND, WAKE UP, MAN!
I KNOW YOU'RE WATCHING ME!
WAKE YOUR ASS UP!
THESE MOTHERFUCKERS
ARE TRYING TO KILL ME, MAN!
WAKE THE FUCK UP!
I NEED YOU RIGHT NOW!
PUT ME ON THE SCREEN!
HEY, FRENCHY!
FRENCHY!
BONJOUR, MOTHERFUCKER.
HEY, LISTEN UP.
THIS THE DEAL.
LET MY BOY GO, AND I'M
GONNA GIVE YOU YOUR SHIT.
SO YOU CAN STOP
FUCKING WITH ME
AND TAKE YOUR OLD ASS
BACK TO FRANCE.
HE DOES MAKE
A STRONG POINT.
[SPEAKING FRENCH]
COME ON.
GET UP.
I GOT $15 MILLION
IN DIAMONDS.
$15 MILLION
SOUNDS TO ME LIKE YOU
PROMISED THEM TO SOMEONE ELSE.
MAN, I DON'T KNOW
WHO THE HELL THAT IS.
RIGHT, RIGHT, RIGHT.
I KNOW WHO IT IS,
BUT I DIDN'T SAY
WE WAS THE ONLY PEOPLE
THAT WANTED
THE DIAMONDS,
BUT I'M THE ONLY ONE
WHO KNOW WHERE THEY AT.
I GOT A FEELING I PUT
A BULLET IN YOUR NUTS,
YOU'RE GONNA TELL ME
WHERE THEY'RE AT.
COME ON, CARMINE,
STOP PLAYING.
YOU CAN'T SHOOT A NIGGER
IN HIS NUTS, MAN.
I NEED MY NUTS.
NOW, LOOK,
IF YOU KILL ME,
YOU WON'T FIND
THEM DIAMONDS.
NOW, YOU NEED ME.
TRUST ME, MAN.
BELIEVE IN ME.
WHAT ABOUT THEM?
MAN, FORGET THEM.
I FIGURE
FOR 10 MILLION,
YOUR BOYS WILL DO
THEIR THING, MAN.
10 MILLION? I THOUGHT
IT WAS 15 MILLION.
MAN, WHAT YOU THINK
I'M DOING
ALL THIS
RUNNING AROUND FOR?
I WANT
SOME DIAMONDS, TOO.
I AIN'T DOING
THIS SHIT FOR FREE.
LOOK AT YOUR STINGY ASS.
THE SECOND
WE GET THOSE STONES,
STICK THAT FUCKING
MOLINON.
WATCH OUT!
AAH!
ONE MORE STEP!
I WAS JUST GOING
TO GET DIAMONDS.
THAT'S ALL I WAS DOING.
WELL, THEN GET 'EM
FOR ME NOW.
[SPEAKING FRENCH]
FUSE TIME, 20 SECONDS.
OR WAS IT 10?
[SPEAKING FRENCH]
I'M READY FOR ANOTHER
CLOSE-UP, MR. DE MILLE.
HEY, FRENCHY!
WHAT THE FUCK'S WRONG WITH YOU?
WHAT YOU SHOOTIN' FOR?
NOW, I'M THE ONLY
MOTHERFUCKER
THAT KNOW WHERE
THE DIAMONDS IS,
SO IF YOU KILL ME,
YOU WON'T FIND 'EM.
SO TELL YOUR BOYS
TO STOP SHOOTING,
OR YOU AIN'T GETTING SHIT.
SHIT.
[DEBRAY SHOUTS IN FRENCH]
YEAH, I WANT TO REPORT
A SHOOTOUT AT--
YEAH, I'LL HOLD.
DEBRAY!
YOU'RE MESSING UP
EVERYTHING.
SHUT UP
AND KEEP MOVING.
WHO THE FUCK
YOU SHOOTING AT?!
HATCHETT!
I WANT THOSE DIAMONDS!
COME ON!
OH! SHIT!
AAH!
YO, AARON!
[GUNSHOT]
AAH!
FIRST...
I'M GONNA SHOOT
YOUR RIGHT KNEE.
THEN I'M GONNA SHOOT
THE OTHER ONE.
YOU GOT THAT...
HOMEY?
UNTIL YOU TELL ME
WHERE MY DIAMONDS ARE.
THAT REALLY
MUST HAVE HURT.
KICK HIS ASS!
KICK THAT
MOTHERFUCKER ASS.
KICK HIS ASS!
WE GOTTA GO, MAN.
WE GOTTA GO.
WE GOTTA GO!
COME ON.
DON'T YOU EVER SAY
I'M YOUR GODDAMN HOMEY!
FRENCHY!
OK, OK, OK, OK.
OK, WHAT?
OK, WE DONE
FUCKED UP, MAN!
LISTEN.
I'M SORRY
I GOT YOU BUSTED.
I WANT YOU TO KNOW,
FOR WHAT IT'S WORTH,
I NEVER DOUBTED YOU.
NEVER ONCE.
THAT AIN'T WORTH
SHIT NOW, MAN,
'CAUSE WE
FIXIN' TO DIE!
BUT THANKS ANYWAY.
YOU'RE WELCOME.
HOLD THIS.
AAH!
THAT WAS BEAUTIFUL.
COME ON, FOLLOW ME.
LET'S GO. COME ON.
WE ALMOST THERE, MAN.
WE ALMOST THERE.
COME ON, MAN, LET'S GO.
[SPEAKING FRENCH]
OH, SHIT.
I GET THE FEELING
YOU STOLE
FROM THE WRONG BUNCH
OF BAD GUYS.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
THIS SHIT AIN'T WORTH
DYING FOR.
IT AIN'T WORTH DYING FOR.
I'M GONNA GIVE 'EM
WHAT THEY WANT.
WHAT?
FUCK THIS.
FRANKLIN.
SWEET JESUS.
HEY!
[SHOUTS IN FRENCH]
HEY, WE SURRENDER!
STOP, EVERYBODY, STOP!
WE SURRENDER!
WE WERE JUST BULLSHITTING.
I GOT YOUR SHIT.
IS THIS WHAT YOU WANT?
HUH?
WELL, COME AND GET IT,
GODDAMN IT!
[SPEAKS FRENCH]
[SHOUTING IN FRENCH]
[SIRENS]
SHIT.
DON'T WORRY.
HE WON'T GET FAR.
AAH!
Russell: AND THAT'S WHEN
THE L.A. COLISEUM
TURNED INTO
A VIRTUAL WAR ZONE.
AMONG THE DEAD,
RAYMOND VILLARD,
LEADER OF A HIGHLY SOPHISTICATED
INTERNATIONAL SMUGGLING RING
AND THE MAN RESPONSIBLE
FOR FRIDAY'S PRISON BREAK.
ALSO DEAD, LAPD DETECTIVE
BOBBY PICKETT.
A DIRTY COP
WHO WE'VE JUST DISCOVERED
WAS VILLARD'S INSIDE MAN.
I HAVE WITH ME NOW
FRANKLIN HATCHETT,
THE MAN ONCE BELIEVED
TO BE RESPONSIBLE
FOR THE EVENTS
AND THE CHAOS
THAT LED TO LAST
NIGHT'S MAYHEM.
FRANKLIN, ANYTHING
YOU'D LIKE TO ADD?
YEAH. HEY, FIRST OF ALL,
I TOLD Y'ALL
I WAS INNOCENT.
FOR THOSE OF Y'ALL
THAT THOUGHT I WAS GUILTY,
Y'ALL KNOW
WHAT Y'ALL CAN DO.
HEY, MAMA,
I LOVE YOU. I'M OK.
PAULA, I LOVE YOU,
TOO, BABY.
I'M GONNA BE HOME LATER ON.
WE GONNA PARTY.
COOK SOME CHICKEN
AND SOME CORN BREAD
AND SOME KOOL-AID,
AND I'M GONNA BE BACK
AT THE CAR WASH MONDAY MORNING.
EVERYTHING ON SALE,
HALF PRICE. PEACE OUT!
OK, THANK YOU, FRANKLIN.
I'M JAMES RUSSELL.
THIS HAS BEEN
A CHANNEL 12 NEWS EXCLUSIVE.
[WEDDING MARCH PLAYING]
Clergyman: IF ANYONE
CAN SHOW JUST CAUSE
WHY THIS COUPLE
SHOULD NOT BE WED,
PLEASE SPEAK NOW
OR FOREVER
HOLD YOUR PEACE.
THE RING, PLEASE?
[WHISPERING]
That's not the ring.
No shit.
Be cool, man. Relax.
It's a wedding gift,
man. Take it.
This is a sacred event.
I know it's sacred.
This is sacred, too.
Just take it. It's legal.
Don't nobody know about it.
How many did you keep?
Enough.
Now get married, man.
Take it.
Lord, forgive me.
He will.
YOU MAY NOW KISS THE BRIDE.
[APPLAUSE]
¶ I KNOW ¶
¶ THERE'S ONLY ¶
¶ ONLY ONE OF YOU ¶
¶ THERE'S NO WAY ¶
¶ THEY COULD HAVE MADE 2 ¶
¶ GIRL, YOU'RE MY REALITY ¶
¶ I'M LOST IN A DREAM ¶
¶ YOU'RE THE FIRST ¶
¶ YOU'RE THE LAST ¶
¶ MY EVERYTHING ¶
¶ FAITH ¶
¶ I'VE GOT FAITH ¶
¶ OHH OHH ¶
¶ OHH OHH OHH OHH ¶
¶ MY FIRST ¶
¶ MY LAST ¶
¶ MY EVERYTHING ¶
¶ YOU ARE
MY EVERYTHING ¶
¶ YOU CAN LOOK ¶
¶ YOU MAY TRY ¶
¶ BUT YOU'LL NEVER
FIND A WOMAN ¶
¶ WHO CAN PLEASE YOU
QUITE THE WAY THAT I DO ¶
¶ I DON'T MEAN
TO BRAG ABOUT IT ¶
¶ BUT YOU CAN'T
GET AROUND IT ¶
¶ AND I'M GONNA BE HERE
FOR YOU ALWAYS ¶
¶ BABY, I'VE LOOKED ¶
¶ FAR AND WIDE ¶
¶ BUT I'VE NEVER FOUND ¶
¶ ANYONE QUITE LIKE YOU ¶
¶ SAY WHAT? ¶
¶ BABY, PLEASE ¶
¶ YOU KNOW I JUST HATE ¶
¶ TO WAIT ¶
¶ YOU'RE THE FIRST ¶
¶ MY LAST ¶
¶ MY EVERYTHING ¶
¶ THERE YOU ARE ¶
¶ FLASHING
THROUGH MY DREAMS ¶
¶ GLAD TO SAY THAT ¶
¶ I MISS YOUR SEXY WAYS ¶
¶ HERE I AM, GIRL ¶
¶ BACK IN YOU AGAIN ¶
¶ SINCE I BEEN GONE ¶
¶ I THOUGHT ABOUT YOU
EVERY DAY ¶
¶ HERE I AM ¶
¶ BACK IN YOU AGAIN ¶
¶ I'M GLAD TO SAY ¶
¶ GLAD TO SAY THAT ¶
¶ I MISS YOUR SEXY WAYS ¶
¶ BABY, HERE I AM ¶
¶ HERE I AM, GIRL ¶
¶ BACK IN YOU AGAIN ¶
¶ ONE MINUTE,
I'M IN JAIL ¶
¶ THE NEXT,
I'M ON THE RUN ¶
¶ BULLETS ARE CHASING ME ¶
¶ FROM GANGSTERS
AND POLICE GUNS ¶
¶ BANG BANG ¶
¶ BUT ALL I DO
IS THINK OF YOU ¶
¶ AND OUR NEW
CHILD TO BE ¶
¶ SUDDENLY,
I'M FREE, YEAH ¶
¶ HERE WE GO ¶
¶ A FUNKY SITUATION ¶
¶ BUT YOU MUST BELIEVE ¶
¶ I'M STILL THE MAN
THAT LOVES YOU ¶
¶ YEAH ¶
¶ GIRL, YOU KNOW ME ¶
¶ AND YOU KNOW
I WOULDN'T HURT NO ONE ¶
¶ YOU'RE FABULOUS,
BABY ¶
¶ SO NOW YOU SEE
I'M ON THE RUN, YEAH ¶
¶ I'M GLAD TO SAY ¶
¶ GLAD TO SAY ¶
¶ I REALLY MISS
YOUR SEXY WAYS ¶
¶ BABY, HERE I AM ¶
¶ HERE I AM ¶
¶ HERE I AM, BABY ¶
¶ BACK IN YOU AGAIN ¶
¶ SINCE I BEEN GONE ¶
¶ I THOUGHT ABOUT YOU
EVERY DAY ¶
¶ BABY, HERE I AM ¶
¶ HERE I AM ¶
¶ HERE I AM, BABY ¶
¶ BACK IN YOU AGAIN ¶
¶ I'M DIGGING YOU, BABY ¶
¶ DIGGING YOU ¶
¶ BACK IN YOU AGAIN ¶
¶ THERE'S NO WAY ¶
¶ NO, NO WAY ¶
¶ YEAH, YEAH ¶
¶ NO WAY ¶
¶ UH-HUH,
NO WAY OUT, BABY ¶
¶ I CAN'T GO NOWHERE ¶
¶ AIN'T GOT
NOWHERE TO TURN ¶
¶ NO WAY ¶
¶ YEAH, YEAH ¶
¶ AIN'T NOW WAY OUT ¶
¶ NO WAY ¶
¶ UH-UH,
CHECK THIS OUT ¶
¶ THERE'S NO WAY OUT ¶
¶ I'M READY TO CALL IT QUITS
FROM ALL THIS SHIT ¶
¶ EVEN RESIGN
FROM THE NIGGERS
¶ I'VE BEEN BALLIN' WITH ¶
¶ I'M SECOND-GUESSING ¶
¶ ALL THIS NEGATIVE ENERGY ¶
¶ IT'S MAKING ME REALIZE
WHY NIGGERS REALLY ENVY ME ¶
¶ I FEEL NO SYMPATHY ¶
¶ IT'S TIGHT ILL ¶
¶ PLUS I GET SLIGHT CHILLS
WHEN I WRITE WILLS ¶
¶ TIRED OF LOOKING AT THESE
UGLY NIGGERS WITH ICE GRILLS ¶
¶ NO TELLING
WHAT I MIGHT FEEL ¶
¶ ABOUT MY GLORY ¶
¶ 2 SIDES
TO EVERY STORY ¶
¶ THAT'S WHY I PRAY TO GOD ¶
¶ HOPING THAT
HE'LL REASSURE ME ¶
¶ THE MORE THE PAIN,
MORE TO GAIN ¶
¶ COME WITH THE TERRITORY ¶
¶ I MIGHT DISPOSE ¶
¶ FEELING LIKE
MY LIFE BEEN CHOSE ¶
¶ ALL I KNOW IN MY LIFE
LOT OF ICE AND HOS ¶
¶ WHEN IT'S ON ¶
¶ MY MAN THERE,
GAT IN HIS HAND ¶
¶ WHAT YOU DOING WHEN YOU
GOT A MASTER PLAN ¶
¶ BUT HACKED AND RAN? ¶